[
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Identify the plural form of 'man'.",
      "options": ["mans", "men", "manen", "menes"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'man' is 'men'.",
      "correctAnswer": "men"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct plural form of 'woman'.",
      "options": ["woman", "womans", "womenn", "women"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'woman' is 'women'.",
      "correctAnswer": "women"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'goose'?",
      "options": ["goos", "gooses", "geese", "geeses"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'goose' is 'geese'.",
      "correctAnswer": "geese"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Identify the plural form of 'mouse'.",
      "options": ["mices", "mouses", "mice", "micees"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'mouse' is 'mice'.",
      "correctAnswer": "mice"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct plural form of 'child'.",
      "options": ["childs", "childen", "childrens", "children"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'child' is 'children'.",
      "correctAnswer": "children"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'tooth'?",
      "options": ["tooths", "teeths", "teeth", "toothes"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'tooth' is 'teeth'.",
      "correctAnswer": "teeth"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Identify the plural form of 'man'.",
      "options": ["mans", "men", "manen", "menes"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'man' is 'men'.",
      "correctAnswer": "men"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct plural form of 'deer'.",
      "options": ["deers", "deer", "deeres", "deeren"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'deer' is 'deer'. It remains the same in plural.",
      "correctAnswer": "deer"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'cactus'?",
      "options": ["cactuss", "cactuses", "cacti", "cacties"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'cactus' is 'cacti'.",
      "correctAnswer": "cacti"
    },
    {
      "category": "Singular or Plural Exercise",
      "questionText": "Identify the plural form of 'child'.",
      "options": ["childs", "childen", "childrens", "children"],
      "explanation": "The plural form of 'child' is 'children'.",
      "correctAnswer": "children"
    },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the type of noun in the sentence: 'dog'",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'dog' is a common noun because it refers to a general class of animals.",
    "correctAnswer": "Common Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "What kind of noun is 'London'?",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'London' is a proper noun because it is the name of a specific place.",
    "correctAnswer": "Proper Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the type of noun in the sentence: 'happiness'",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'happiness' is an abstract noun because it refers to a concept or idea.",
    "correctAnswer": "Abstract Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "What kind of noun is 'table'?",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'table' is a concrete noun because it is a physical, tangible object.",
    "correctAnswer": "Concrete Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the type of noun in the sentence: 'team'",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'team' is a common noun because it refers to a general group of people.",
    "correctAnswer": "Common Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "What kind of noun is 'freedom'?",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'freedom' is an abstract noun because it refers to a concept or state.",
    "correctAnswer": "Abstract Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the type of noun in the sentence: 'Paris'",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'Paris' is a proper noun because it is the name of a specific city.",
    "correctAnswer": "Proper Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "What kind of noun is 'river'?",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'river' is a common noun because it refers to a general natural feature.",
    "correctAnswer": "Common Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the type of noun in the sentence: 'intelligence'",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'intelligence' is an abstract noun because it refers to a mental quality.",
    "correctAnswer": "Abstract Noun"
  },
  {
    "category": "Kinds of Nouns Exercise",
    "questionText": "What kind of noun is 'book'?",
    "options": ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Abstract Noun", "Concrete Noun"],
    "explanation": "'book' is a concrete noun because it is a physical object.",
    "correctAnswer": "Concrete Noun"
  },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'cat'?",
      "options": ["cats", "caties", "cates", "catz"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'cat' is 'cats' by adding 's'.",
      "correctAnswer": "cats"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'box'?",
      "options": ["boxs", "boxes", "boxen", "boxies"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'box' is 'boxes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "boxes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'bush'?",
      "options": ["bushes", "bushs", "bushi", "bushies"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'bush' is 'bushes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "bushes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'potato'?",
      "options": ["potatos", "potatoes", "potaties", "potatii"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'potato' is 'potatoes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "potatoes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'church'?",
      "options": ["churchies", "churchs", "churches", "churchen"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'church' is 'churches' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "churches"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'bus'?",
      "options": ["busen", "buses", "buss", "bussies"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'bus' is 'buses' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "buses"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'hero'?",
      "options": ["heroines", "heros", "heroes", "heroen"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'hero' is 'heroes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "heroes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'wolf'?",
      "options": ["wolves", "wolfs", "wolven", "wolfies"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'wolf' is 'wolves' by changing 'f' to 'v' and adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "wolves"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'baby'?",
      "options": ["babyes", "babies", "babyen", "babys"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'baby' is 'babies' by changing 'y' to 'ies'.",
      "correctAnswer": "babies"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'city'?",
      "options": ["cityes", "citien", "cities", "citii"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'city' is 'cities' by changing 'y' to 'ies'.",
      "correctAnswer": "cities"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'fox'?",
      "options": ["foxen", "foxes", "foxis", "foxies"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'fox' is 'foxes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "foxes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'knife'?",
      "options": ["knifes", "knives", "knivees", "kniven"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'knife' is 'knives' by changing 'f' to 'v' and adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "knives"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'child'?",
      "options": ["childs", "childen", "childrens", "children"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'child' is 'children' by changing 'i' to 'e' and adding 'ren'.",
      "correctAnswer": "children"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'man'?",
      "options": ["mans", "men", "menes", "menn"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'man' is 'men' by changing 'a' to 'e'.",
      "correctAnswer": "men"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'woman'?",
      "options": ["woman", "womans", "womenn", "women"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'woman' is 'women' by changing 'a' to 'e'.",
      "correctAnswer": "women"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'potato'?",
      "options": ["potatos", "potatoes", "potaties", "potatii"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'potato' is 'potatoes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "potatoes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'mouse'?",
      "options": ["mices", "mouses", "mice", "micees"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'mouse' is 'mice' by changing 'ouse' to 'ice'.",
      "correctAnswer": "mice"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'church'?",
      "options": ["churchies", "churchs", "churches", "churchen"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'church' is 'churches' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "churches"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'child'?",
      "options": ["childs", "childen", "childrens", "children"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'child' is 'children' by changing 'i' to 'e' and adding 'ren'.",
      "correctAnswer": "children"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Spelling Rule Exercise",
      "questionText": "What is the plural of 'tomato'?",
      "options": ["tomatoz", "tomatoes", "tomatoes", "tomatii"],
      "explanation": "The plural of 'tomato' is 'tomatoes' by adding 'es'.",
      "correctAnswer": "tomatoes"
    },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Which pronoun is used to refer to a person or people as the object of a sentence?",
    "options": ["he", "we", "she", "them"],
    "explanation": "The pronoun 'them' is used to refer to a person or people as the object of a sentence.",
    "correctAnswer": "them"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "What is the possessive pronoun for the third person singular female?",
    "options": ["her", "hers", "him", "his"],
    "explanation": "The possessive pronoun for the third person singular female is 'hers'.",
    "correctAnswer": "hers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the reflexive pronoun in the following sentence: 'She cooked dinner for herself.'",
    "options": ["She", "cooked", "dinner", "herself"],
    "explanation": "The reflexive pronoun in the sentence is 'herself'.",
    "correctAnswer": "herself"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Which pronoun can be used to refer to a non-specific person?",
    "options": ["they", "you", "I", "it"],
    "explanation": "The pronoun 'they' can be used to refer to a non-specific person.",
    "correctAnswer": "they"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "In the sentence 'John and ____ went to the store,' which pronoun should fill the blank?",
    "options": ["he", "him", "his", "they"],
    "explanation": "The correct pronoun to fill the blank is 'he'.",
    "correctAnswer": "he"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "What is the singular, gender-neutral pronoun used to refer to a person?",
    "options": ["he", "she", "they", "it"],
    "explanation": "The singular, gender-neutral pronoun used to refer to a person is 'they'.",
    "correctAnswer": "they"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Which pronoun is used when addressing someone directly?",
    "options": ["he", "him", "his", "you"],
    "explanation": "The pronoun used when addressing someone directly is 'you'.",
    "correctAnswer": "you"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "What is the object pronoun for the first person singular?",
    "options": ["me", "myself", "I", "mine"],
    "explanation": "The object pronoun for the first person singular is 'me'.",
    "correctAnswer": "me"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Identify the possessive pronoun in the following sentence: 'The book is yours.'",
    "options": ["The", "book", "is", "yours"],
    "explanation": "The possessive pronoun in the sentence is 'yours'.",
    "correctAnswer": "yours"
  },
  {
    "category": "Checking Understanding of Pronoun Exercise",
    "questionText": "Which pronoun is used to refer to a thing or an animal?",
    "options": ["he", "they", "it", "she"],
    "explanation": "The pronoun 'it' is used to refer to a thing or an animal.",
    "correctAnswer": "it"
  },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "Which kind of pronoun is used to refer to a specific person, place, or thing?",
      "options": ["Personal Pronoun", "Reflexive Pronoun", "Demonstrative Pronoun", "Indefinite Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "A Demonstrative Pronoun is used to point to a specific person, place, or thing.",
      "correctAnswer": "Demonstrative Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "What type of pronoun is 'she'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Personal Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'She' is a Personal Pronoun used to refer to a female person.",
      "correctAnswer": "Personal Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "Which kind of pronoun is 'whose'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun", "Reflexive Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Whose' is an Interrogative Pronoun used to ask about ownership.",
      "correctAnswer": "Interrogative Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "What type of pronoun is 'itself'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Demonstrative Pronoun", "Reflexive Pronoun", "Indefinite Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Itself' is a Reflexive Pronoun used to refer back to the subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Reflexive Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "Which kind of pronoun is 'anybody'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Indefinite Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Anybody' is an Indefinite Pronoun used to refer to an unspecified person.",
      "correctAnswer": "Indefinite Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "What type of pronoun is 'my'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Personal Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'My' is a Possessive Pronoun used to show ownership.",
      "correctAnswer": "Possessive Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "Which kind of pronoun is 'who'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Indefinite Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun", "Reflexive Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Who' is an Interrogative Pronoun used to ask about people.",
      "correctAnswer": "Interrogative Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "What type of pronoun is 'that'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Demonstrative Pronoun", "Interrogative Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'That' is a Demonstrative Pronoun used to indicate a specific thing.",
      "correctAnswer": "Demonstrative Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "Which kind of pronoun is 'which'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Demonstrative Pronoun", "Indefinite Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Which' is a Relative Pronoun used to introduce relative clauses.",
      "correctAnswer": "Relative Pronoun"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Pronoun Exercise",
      "questionText": "What type of pronoun is 'them'?",
      "options": ["Relative Pronoun", "Possessive Pronoun", "Personal Pronoun", "Demonstrative Pronoun"],
      "explanation": "'Them' is a Personal Pronoun used to refer to a group of people.",
      "correctAnswer": "Personal Pronoun"
    },

    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Find the pronoun in the sentence: 'She is reading a book.'",
      "options": ["She", "reading", "a", "book"],
      "explanation": "'She' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "She"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Locate the pronoun in the sentence: 'They went to the park.'",
      "options": ["They", "went", "to", "park"],
      "explanation": "'They' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "They"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Identify the pronoun in the sentence: 'I like ice cream.'",
      "options": ["I", "like", "ice", "cream"],
      "explanation": "'I' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "I"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Pick out the pronoun in the sentence: 'He sings beautifully.'",
      "options": ["He", "sings", "beautifully", "He sings"],
      "explanation": "'He' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "He"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose the pronoun in the sentence: 'We are going to the movies.'",
      "options": ["We", "are", "going", "movies"],
      "explanation": "'We' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "We"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Spot the pronoun in the sentence: 'She and he are friends.'",
      "options": ["She", "he", "are", "friends"],
      "explanation": "'She' and 'he' are the pronouns in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "She"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Locate the pronoun in the sentence: 'It is raining outside.'",
      "options": ["It", "is", "raining", "outside"],
      "explanation": "'It' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "It"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Find the pronoun in the sentence: 'My cat loves to play.'",
      "options": ["My", "cat", "loves", "play"],
      "explanation": "'My' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "My"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Identify the pronoun in the sentence: 'The dog chased its tail.'",
      "options": ["The", "dog", "chased", "its"],
      "explanation": "'Its' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "its"
    },
    {
      "category": "Finding Pronoun in a Sentence လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Pick out the pronoun in the sentence: 'You are doing great.'",
      "options": ["You", "are", "doing", "great"],
      "explanation": "'You' is the pronoun in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "You"
    },

    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Please pick the adjective that vividly describes a noun:",
      "options": ["Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative", "Demonstrative"],
      "explanation": "A Descriptive Adjective vividly describes a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Descriptive"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose the adjective that provides specific quantity information about a noun:",
      "options": ["Numeral", "Descriptive", "Quantitative", "Demonstrative"],
      "explanation": "A Numeral Adjective provides specific quantity information about a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Numeral"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Identify the adjective used to indicate or point out a specific noun:",
      "options": ["Demonstrative", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "A Demonstrative Adjective is used to indicate or point out a specific noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Demonstrative"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose the adjective that helps us ask questions about a noun:",
      "options": ["Interrogative", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "Interrogative Adjectives help us ask questions about a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Interrogative"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Pick the adjective indicating ownership or possession:",
      "options": ["Possessive", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "Possessive Adjectives indicate ownership or possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "Possessive"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose the adjectives derived from proper nouns and are capitalized:",
      "options": ["Proper", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "Adjectives derived from proper nouns and capitalized are Proper Adjectives.",
      "correctAnswer": "Proper"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Select the adjective that conveys strong emotion or surprise:",
      "options": ["Exclamatory", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "Exclamatory Adjectives convey strong emotion or surprise.",
      "correctAnswer": "Exclamatory"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "When an adjective specifies the exact quantity of a noun, it's called:",
      "options": ["Numeral", "Descriptive", "Quantitative", "Demonstrative"],
      "explanation": "A Numeral Adjective specifies the exact quantity of a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Numeral"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "What type of adjective provides information about the amount or proportion of a noun?",
      "options": ["Quantitative", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Demonstrative"],
      "explanation": "A Quantitative Adjective gives us information about the amount or proportion of a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Quantitative"
    },
    {
      "category": "Kinds of Adjectives လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Adjectives that help us ask questions about a noun are known as:",
      "options": ["Interrogative", "Descriptive", "Numeral", "Quantitative"],
      "explanation": "Interrogative Adjectives help us ask questions about a noun.",
      "correctAnswer": "Interrogative"
    },

    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Find the adjective: The cat is playful.",
      "options": ["cat", "is", "playful", "The"],
      "explanation": "The word 'playful' is an adjective describing the cat.",
      "correctAnswer": "playful"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Find the adjective: The sky turned dark in the evening.",
      "options": ["sky", "turned", "dark", "evening"],
      "explanation": "'Dark' is the adjective describing the sky.",
      "correctAnswer": "dark"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "In the sentence, 'She wore a beautiful dress,' what word is the adjective?",
      "options": ["She", "wore", "beautiful", "dress"],
      "explanation": "'Beautiful' is the adjective describing the dress.",
      "correctAnswer": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Identify the adjective: The flowers in the garden are colorful.",
      "options": ["flowers", "garden", "are", "colorful"],
      "explanation": "'Colorful' is the adjective describing the flowers.",
      "correctAnswer": "colorful"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Which word is the adjective? It was a rainy day.",
      "options": ["It", "was", "rainy", "day"],
      "explanation": "'Rainy' is the adjective describing the day.",
      "correctAnswer": "rainy"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Find the adjective: The big elephant walked slowly.",
      "options": ["big", "elephant", "walked", "slowly"],
      "explanation": "'Big' is the adjective describing the elephant.",
      "correctAnswer": "big"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "In the sentence, 'The tall boy played basketball,' which word is the adjective?",
      "options": ["The", "tall", "boy", "played"],
      "explanation": "'Tall' is the adjective describing the boy.",
      "correctAnswer": "tall"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Identify the adjective: The cozy room was nicely decorated.",
      "options": ["cozy", "room", "was", "nicely"],
      "explanation": "'Cozy' is the adjective describing the room.",
      "correctAnswer": "cozy"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Which word is the adjective? She found a shiny coin.",
      "options": ["She", "found", "shiny", "coin"],
      "explanation": "'Shiny' is the adjective describing the coin.",
      "correctAnswer": "shiny"
    },
    {
      "category": "Find the Adjective",
      "questionText": "Find the adjective: The little girl had a cute puppy.",
      "options": ["little", "girl", "had", "cute"],
      "explanation": "'Cute' is the adjective describing the puppy.",
      "correctAnswer": "cute"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose possessive adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "His",
        "Five",
        "Whose",
        "Many"
      ],
      "explanation": "'His' is a possessive adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "His"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose quantitative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "Which",
        "Several",
        "My",
        "Their"
      ],
      "explanation": "'Several' is a quantitative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "Several"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose demonstrative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "Your",
        "Such",
        "This",
        "Few"
      ],
      "explanation": "'This' is a demonstrative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "This"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose interrogative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "Most",
        "Those",
        "What",
        "Each"
      ],
      "explanation": "'What' is an interrogative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose possessive adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "Either",
        "Whose",
        "Many",
        "Her"
      ],
      "explanation": "'Her' is a possessive adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "Her"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose quantitative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "These",
        "Few",
        "His",
        "Several"
      ],
      "explanation": "'Few' is a quantitative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "Few"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose demonstrative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "Any",
        "Some",
        "That",
        "Every"
      ],
      "explanation": "'That' is a demonstrative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "That"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose interrogative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "My",
        "What",
        "Her",
        "Both"
      ],
      "explanation": "'What' is an interrogative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose possessive adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "How many",
        "His",
        "Many",
        "Each"
      ],
      "explanation": "'His' is a possessive adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "His"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective အမျိုးစားလေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Choose quantitative adjective given below.",
      "options": [
        "These",
        "Whose",
        "Nice",
        "Several"
      ],
      "explanation": "'Several' is a quantitative adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "Several"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'running' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "Yes, 'running' is a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'apple' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "No, 'apple' is not a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "No"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'jumped' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "Yes, 'jumped' is a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'happiness' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "No, 'happiness' is not a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "No"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'swimming' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "Yes, 'swimming' is a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'table' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "No, 'table' is not a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "No"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'writing' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "Yes, 'writing' is a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'tree' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "No, 'tree' is not a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "No"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'sang' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "Yes, 'sang' is a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Is the word 'cloud' a verb?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "explanation": "No, 'cloud' is not a verb.",
      "correctAnswer": "No"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'run' in the sentence 'She runs every morning.' a linking verb or an action verb?",
      "options": ["Linking verb", "Action verb"],
      "explanation": "'runs' is an action verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Action verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'seem' in the sentence 'The movie seems interesting.' a linking verb or an action verb?",
      "options": ["Linking verb", "Action verb"],
      "explanation": "'seems' is a linking verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Linking verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'taste' in the sentence 'The soup tastes delicious.' a linking verb or an action verb?",
      "options": ["Linking verb", "Action verb"],
      "explanation": "'tastes' is a linking verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Linking verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'read' in the sentence 'She reads books every day.' a transitive verb or an intransitive verb?",
      "options": ["Transitive verb", "Intransitive verb"],
      "explanation": "'reads' is a transitive verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Transitive verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'sleep' in the sentence 'He sleeps peacefully.' a transitive verb or an intransitive verb?",
      "options": ["Transitive verb", "Intransitive verb"],
      "explanation": "'sleeps' is an intransitive verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Intransitive verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'feel' in the sentence 'She feels tired after work.' a dynamic verb or a stative verb?",
      "options": ["Dynamic verb", "Stative verb"],
      "explanation": "'feels' is a stative verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Stative verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'run' in the sentence 'They run marathons.' a dynamic verb or a stative verb?",
      "options": ["Dynamic verb", "Stative verb"],
      "explanation": "'run' is a dynamic verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Dynamic verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'sing' in the sentence 'She sings beautifully.' an infinitive verb or a gerund verb?",
      "options": ["Infinitive verb", "Gerund verb"],
      "explanation": "'sings' is an infinitive verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'swimming' in the sentence 'She enjoys swimming.' an infinitive verb or a gerund verb?",
      "options": ["Infinitive verb", "Gerund verb"],
      "explanation": "'swimming' is a gerund verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund verb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Is the verb 'learn' in the sentence 'He wants to learn programming.' an auxiliary verb or a main verb?",
      "options": ["Auxiliary verb", "Main verb"],
      "explanation": "'learn' is a main verb in this sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Main verb"
    },

    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Identify the adverb in the sentence: 'She sings beautifully.'",
      "options": ["She", "beautifully", "sings"],
      "explanation": "'beautifully' is the adverb in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "beautifully"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'quickly' in the sentence: 'He ran quickly to catch the bus.'?",
      "options": ["Adverb of time", "Adverb of manner", "Adverb of frequency", "Adverb of place"],
      "explanation": "'quickly' is an adverb of manner in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Adverb of manner"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In which sentence is the word 'today' used as an adverb of time?",
      "options": [
        "She will visit us today.",
        "The weather is great today.",
        "He is a teacher today.",
        "I can't go to the party today."
      ],
      "explanation": "'She will visit us today.' uses 'today' as an adverb of time.",
      "correctAnswer": "She will visit us today."
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Choose the adverb of frequency in the sentence: 'They always arrive early.'",
      "options": ["They", "always", "arrive", "early"],
      "explanation": "'always' is the adverb of frequency in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "always"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Identify the adverbial phrase in the sentence: 'She danced in the moonlight.'",
      "options": ["She", "danced", "in the moonlight"],
      "explanation": "'in the moonlight' is the adverbial phrase in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "in the moonlight"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'yesterday' in the sentence: 'He finished the project yesterday.'?",
      "options": ["Adverb of time", "Adverb of manner", "Adverb of frequency", "Adverb of place"],
      "explanation": "'yesterday' is an adverb of time in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Adverb of time"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Choose the adverb of place in the sentence: 'She looked everywhere for her keys.'",
      "options": ["She", "looked", "everywhere", "for her keys"],
      "explanation": "'everywhere' is the adverb of place in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "everywhere"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'often' in the sentence: 'They often go hiking.'?",
      "options": ["Adverb of time", "Adverb of manner", "Adverb of frequency", "Adverb of place"],
      "explanation": "'often' is an adverb of frequency in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "Adverb of frequency"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In which sentence is the word 'here' used as an adverb of place?",
      "options": [
        "She is here.",
        "Here comes the train.",
        "I will go there.",
        "He studies well here."
      ],
      "explanation": "'She is here.' uses 'here' as an adverb of place.",
      "correctAnswer": "She is here."
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Choose the adverb of manner in the sentence: 'She sings beautifully.'",
      "options": ["She", "sings", "beautifully"],
      "explanation": "'beautifully' is the adverb of manner in the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "beautifully"
    },

    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the adverb in 'She sings loudly.'?",
      "options": ["She", "sings", "loudly"],
      "explanation": "'loudly' is the adverb.",
      "correctAnswer": "loudly"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'quickly' in 'He ran quickly.'?",
      "options": ["Time", "Manner", "Frequency", "Place"],
      "explanation": "'quickly' is an adverb of manner.",
      "correctAnswer": "Manner"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which sentence has the adverb of time? \n1. She cooks well. \n2. They will come tomorrow. \n3. The cat meowed loudly.",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
      "explanation": "Sentence 2 has the adverb of time.",
      "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Pick the adverb of frequency in 'They always smile.'",
      "options": ["They", "always", "smile"],
      "explanation": "'always' is the adverb of frequency.",
      "correctAnswer": "always"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which phrase is the adverbial phrase in 'He works in the garden.'?",
      "options": ["He", "works", "in the garden"],
      "explanation": "'in the garden' is the adverbial phrase.",
      "correctAnswer": "in the garden"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'yesterday' in 'She finished her homework yesterday.'?",
      "options": ["Time", "Manner", "Frequency", "Place"],
      "explanation": "'yesterday' is an adverb of time.",
      "correctAnswer": "Time"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the adverb of place in 'They walked here.'?",
      "options": ["They", "walked", "here"],
      "explanation": "'here' is the adverb of place.",
      "correctAnswer": "here"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "What kind of adverb is 'often' in 'They often visit the park.'?",
      "options": ["Time", "Manner", "Frequency", "Place"],
      "explanation": "'often' is an adverb of frequency.",
      "correctAnswer": "Frequency"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which sentence has the adverb of place? \n1. She dances gracefully. \n2. The party is tonight. \n3. He lives here.",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
      "explanation": "Sentence 3 has the adverb of place.",
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the adverb in 'He sings joyfully.'?",
      "options": ["He", "sings", "joyfully"],
      "explanation": "'joyfully' is the adverb.",
      "correctAnswer": "joyfully"
    },

    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the preposition in 'The cat is on the roof.'?",
      "options": ["cat", "roof", "on"],
      "explanation": "'on' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In 'She is reading a book in the library,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["She", "reading", "book", "library"],
      "explanation": "'in' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What is the preposition in 'The keys are between the cushions.'?",
      "options": ["keys", "cushions", "between"],
      "explanation": "'between' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "between"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Pick the preposition in 'They met at the park.'",
      "options": ["They", "met", "park", "at"],
      "explanation": "'at' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "at"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the preposition in 'The cat is hiding under the table.'?",
      "options": ["cat", "hiding", "table", "under"],
      "explanation": "'under' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "under"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In 'She walked by the river,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["walked", "river", "by"],
      "explanation": "'by' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "by"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What is the preposition in 'The pen is in the drawer.'?",
      "options": ["pen", "drawer", "in"],
      "explanation": "'in' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Pick the preposition in 'They will meet on Monday.'",
      "options": ["meet", "Monday", "on"],
      "explanation": "'on' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which word is the preposition in 'The book is beside the laptop.'?",
      "options": ["book", "beside", "laptop"],
      "explanation": "'beside' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "beside"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In 'He lives in the city,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["lives", "city", "in"],
      "explanation": "'in' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },

    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Choose the preposition: 'The cat is under the table.'",
      "options": ["cat", "under", "table"],
      "explanation": "'under' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "under"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "In 'She walked to the park,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["walked", "park", "to"],
      "explanation": "'to' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "to"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Find the preposition in 'He's sitting beside the window.'",
      "options": ["He's", "sitting", "beside", "window"],
      "explanation": "'beside' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "beside"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Choose the preposition: 'The book is on the shelf.'",
      "options": ["book", "on", "shelf"],
      "explanation": "'on' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Find the preposition in 'She traveled by train.'",
      "options": ["She", "traveled", "by", "train"],
      "explanation": "'by' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "by"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Spot the preposition: 'They played in the park.'",
      "options": ["They", "played", "in", "park"],
      "explanation": "'in' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "In 'The cat jumped off the wall,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["cat", "jumped", "off", "wall"],
      "explanation": "'off' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "off"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Find the preposition in 'She's going to the store.'",
      "options": ["She's", "going", "to", "store"],
      "explanation": "'to' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "to"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Spot the preposition: 'They sat under the tree.'",
      "options": ["They", "sat", "under", "tree"],
      "explanation": "'under' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "under"
    },
    {
      "category": "Preposition ဝိဘတ်လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "In 'He lives near the beach,' what is the preposition?",
      "options": ["lives", "near", "beach"],
      "explanation": "'near' is the preposition.",
      "correctAnswer": "near"
    },

    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which conjunction connects two contrasting ideas: 'He is tired, but he wants to finish the work.'?",
      "options": ["and", "or", "but", "so"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the conjunction that connects contrasting ideas.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What type of conjunction is 'although' in 'Although it rained, we went for a walk.'?",
      "options": ["Coordinating conjunction", "Subordinating conjunction", "Correlative conjunction"],
      "explanation": "'although' is a subordinating conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "Subordinating conjunction"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In 'She likes both tea and coffee,' what is the conjunction?",
      "options": ["likes", "both", "tea", "and"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which conjunction is missing: 'I wanted to go swimming, ____ it started raining.'?",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the missing conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What kind of conjunction is 'either...or' in 'You can either study or play.'?",
      "options": ["Coordinating conjunction", "Subordinating conjunction", "Correlative conjunction"],
      "explanation": "'either...or' is a correlative conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "Correlative conjunction"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Choose the conjunction in 'She is tall, yet graceful.'",
      "options": ["She", "is", "tall", "yet"],
      "explanation": "'yet' is the conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "yet"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which conjunction connects these sentences: 'He likes ice cream. She prefers cake.'?",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the conjunction that connects the sentences.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What type of conjunction is 'neither...nor' in 'Neither the cat nor the dog likes water.'?",
      "options": ["Coordinating conjunction", "Subordinating conjunction", "Correlative conjunction"],
      "explanation": "'neither...nor' is a correlative conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "Correlative conjunction"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "In 'He plays soccer as well as basketball,' what is the conjunction?",
      "options": ["plays", "soccer", "as well as", "basketball"],
      "explanation": "'as well as' is the conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "as well as"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Which conjunction is missing: 'She wanted to dance ____ sing.'?",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'or' is the missing conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "or"
    },

    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Complete the sentence: 'I wanted to go to the movies, ____ my friends wanted to stay home.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Fill in the blank: 'She likes both tea ____ coffee.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct conjunction: 'He enjoys swimming, ____ he doesn't like diving.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Complete the sentence: 'She is talented ____ hardworking.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Fill in the blank: 'He not only likes pizza, ____ he also enjoys pasta.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct conjunction: 'You can either join the club, ____ you can participate in the event.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'or' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "or"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Complete the sentence: 'She loves to dance, ____ she enjoys singing.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Fill in the blank: 'He worked hard, ____ he didn't succeed.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct conjunction: 'They played in the park, ____ they also had a picnic.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'and' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "and"
    },
    {
      "category": "Conjunctions လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Complete the sentence: 'I wanted to go shopping, ____ I didn't have enough money.'",
      "options": ["and", "but", "so", "or"],
      "explanation": "'but' is the correct conjunction.",
      "correctAnswer": "but"
    },
    
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "She ____ a doctor.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'is'.",
          "correctAnswer": "is"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "They ____ students at the university.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'They' is 'are'.",
          "correctAnswer": "are"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "I ____ excited about the trip.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'I' is 'am'.",
          "correctAnswer": "am"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "The cat ____ sleeping on the couch.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The cat' is 'is'.",
          "correctAnswer": "is"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "You ____ a talented musician.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'You' is 'are'.",
          "correctAnswer": "are"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "The flowers ____ beautiful in the garden.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The flowers' is 'are'.",
          "correctAnswer": "are"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "He ____ an engineer at the company.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'He' is 'is'.",
          "correctAnswer": "is"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "My friends ____ coming to the party tonight.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'My friends' is 'are'.",
          "correctAnswer": "are"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "It ____ important to finish the project on time.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'It' is 'is'.",
          "correctAnswer": "is"
      },
      {
          "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
          "questionText": "She and her brother ____ excellent swimmers.",
          "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
          "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subjects 'She and her brother' is 'are'.",
          "correctAnswer": "are"
      },
      
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ she a teacher?",
            "options": ["Am", "Is", "Are"],
            "explanation": "The correct question formation for the subject 'she' is 'Is she a teacher?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Is"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ you a student?",
            "options": ["Am", "Is", "Are"],
            "explanation": "The correct question formation for the subject 'you' is 'Are you a student?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Are"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ it raining outside?",
            "options": ["Am", "Is", "Are"],
            "explanation": "The correct question formation for the subject 'it' is 'Is it raining outside?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Is"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ they coming to the party?",
            "options": ["Am", "Is", "Are"],
            "explanation": "The correct question formation for the subject 'they' is 'Are they coming to the party?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Are"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "She ____ a doctor.",
            "options": ["am not", "isn't", "aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative statement for the subject 'she' is 'She isn't a doctor.'",
            "correctAnswer": "isn't"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "We ____ at the office.",
            "options": ["am not", "isn't", "aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative statement for the subject 'we' is 'We aren't at the office.'",
            "correctAnswer": "aren't"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "They ____ happy with the results.",
            "options": ["am not", "isn't", "aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative statement for the subject 'they' is 'They aren't happy with the results.'",
            "correctAnswer": "aren't"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "It ____ a good idea.",
            "options": ["am not", "isn't", "aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative statement for the subject 'it' is 'It isn't a good idea.'",
            "correctAnswer": "isn't"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ she a student?",
            "options": ["Am not", "Isn't", "Aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative question formation for the subject 'she' is 'Isn't she a student?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Isn't"
        },
        {
            "category": "Verb to be(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
            "questionText": "____ they coming to the meeting?",
            "options": ["Am not", "Isn't", "Aren't"],
            "explanation": "The correct negative question formation for the subject 'they' is 'Aren't they coming to the meeting?'",
            "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
        },

        
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "She ____ a teacher last year.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'was'.",
              "correctAnswer": "was"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "We ____ at the park yesterday.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'We' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "They ____ excited about the trip.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'They' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "It ____ a beautiful day yesterday.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'It' is 'was'.",
              "correctAnswer": "was"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "You ____ my best friend in high school.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'You' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "The flowers ____ beautiful last spring.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The flowers' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "He ____ tired after the long journey.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'He' is 'was'.",
              "correctAnswer": "was"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "My friends ____ at the party last night.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'My friends' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "The weather ____ perfect for the picnic.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The weather' is 'was'.",
              "correctAnswer": "was"
          },
          {
              "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
              "questionText": "She and her brother ____ excited about the movie.",
              "options": ["was", "were"],
              "explanation": "The correct past tense of the verb 'to be' for the subjects 'She and her brother' is 'were'.",
              "correctAnswer": "were"
          },

          
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "She ____ a teacher last year.",
                "options": ["was", "were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense statement for the subject 'She' is 'She was a teacher last year.'",
                "correctAnswer": "was"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "They ____ excited about the trip.",
                "options": ["was", "were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense statement for the subject 'They' is 'They were excited about the trip.'",
                "correctAnswer": "were"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ you at the park yesterday?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Were you at the park yesterday?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Were"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ it a beautiful day yesterday?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense question for the subject 'it' is 'Was it a beautiful day yesterday?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Was"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "She ____ not a doctor last year.",
                "options": ["was", "were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense negative statement for the subject 'She' is 'She was not a doctor last year.'",
                "correctAnswer": "was"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "We ____ not at the party last night.",
                "options": ["was", "were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense negative statement for the subject 'We' is 'We were not at the party last night.'",
                "correctAnswer": "were"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ you excited about the game?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Were you excited about the game?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Were"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ the weather nice yesterday?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense question for the subject 'the weather' is 'Was the weather nice yesterday?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Was"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ she not happy about the results?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense negative question for the subject 'she' is 'Wasn't she happy about the results?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Was"
            },
            {
                "category": "Verb to be(was/were) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                "questionText": "____ they not at home when you arrived?",
                "options": ["Was", "Were"],
                "explanation": "The correct past tense negative question for the subject 'they' is 'Weren't they at home when you arrived?'",
                "correctAnswer": "Were"
            },

            
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "She ____ a teacher next year.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "We ____ at the park tomorrow.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'We' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "They ____ excited about the trip.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'They' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "It ____ a beautiful day tomorrow.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'It' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "You ____ my best friend in the future.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'You' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "The flowers ____ in full bloom next spring.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The flowers' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "He ____ tired after the long journey.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'He' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "My friends ____ at the party tomorrow night.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'My friends' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "The weather ____ perfect for the picnic next weekend.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The weather' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              {
                  "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
                  "questionText": "She and her brother ____ excited about the movie.",
                  "options": ["will be", "shall be"],
                  "explanation": "The correct future tense of the verb 'to be' for the subjects 'She and her brother' is 'will be'.",
                  "correctAnswer": "will be"
              },
              
            
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "She ____ a teacher next year.",
                    "options": ["will be", "won't be"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense statement for the subject 'She' is 'She will be a teacher next year.'",
                    "correctAnswer": "will be"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "They ____ excited about the trip.",
                    "options": ["will be", "won't be"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense statement for the subject 'They' is 'They will be excited about the trip.'",
                    "correctAnswer": "will be"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ you at the park tomorrow?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Will you be at the park tomorrow?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Will"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ it a beautiful day tomorrow?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense question for the subject 'it' is 'Will it be a beautiful day tomorrow?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Will"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "She ____ not a doctor next year.",
                    "options": ["will be", "won't be"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense negative statement for the subject 'She' is 'She won't be a doctor next year.'",
                    "correctAnswer": "won't be"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "We ____ not at the party tomorrow night.",
                    "options": ["will be", "won't be"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense negative statement for the subject 'We' is 'We won't be at the party tomorrow night.'",
                    "correctAnswer": "won't be"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ you excited about the game?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Will you be excited about the game?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Will"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ the weather nice tomorrow?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense question for the subject 'the weather' is 'Will the weather be nice tomorrow?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Will"
                },
                {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ she not happy about the results?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense negative question for the subject 'she' is 'Won't she be happy about the results?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Won't"
                },
  {
                    "category": "Verb to be (will be) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း 2",
                    "questionText": "____ they not at home when you arrive?",
                    "options": ["Will", "Won't"],
                    "explanation": "The correct future tense negative question for the subject 'they' is 'Won't they be at home when you arrive?'",
                    "correctAnswer": "Won't"
  },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ a teacher for five years.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'has been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "We ____ friends since childhood.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'We' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ working on this project for months.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'They' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "It ____ a busy day at the office.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'It' is 'has been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "You ____ my best friend for a long time.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'You' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "The flowers ____ in full bloom all spring.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The flowers' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "He ____ busy with work lately.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'He' is 'has been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "My friends ____ preparing for the exam.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'My friends' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "The weather ____ lovely these past few days.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The weather' is 'has been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She and her brother ____ studying for the test.",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense of the verb 'to be' for the subjects 'She and her brother' is 'have been'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ a teacher for five years.",
      "options": ["has been", "have been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'She' is 'She has been a teacher for five years.'",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ you to the party lately?",
      "options": ["Have", "Has"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Have you been to the party lately?'",
      "correctAnswer": "Have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ not working on this project for months.",
      "options": ["hasn't been", "haven't been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense negative statement for the subject 'They' is 'They haven't been working on this project for months.'",
      "correctAnswer": "haven't been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ it a busy week at the office?",
      "options": ["Has", "Have"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense question for the subject 'it' is 'Has it been a busy week at the office?'",
      "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "You ____ my best friend for a long time, haven't you?",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'You' is 'You have been my best friend for a long time, haven't you?'",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The flowers ____ in full bloom all spring, haven't they?",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'The flowers' is 'The flowers have been in full bloom all spring, haven't they?'",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ busy with work lately, hasn't he?",
      "options": ["has been", "have been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'He' is 'He has been busy with work lately, hasn't he?'",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "My friends ____ preparing for the exam, haven't they?",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'My friends' is 'My friends have been preparing for the exam, haven't they?'",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The weather ____ lovely these past few days, hasn't it?",
      "options": ["has been", "have been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subject 'The weather' is 'The weather has been lovely these past few days, hasn't it?'",
      "correctAnswer": "has been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She and her brother ____ studying for the test, haven't they?",
      "options": ["have been", "has been"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense statement for the subjects 'She and her brother' is 'She and her brother have been studying for the test, haven't they?'",
      "correctAnswer": "have been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ not been to the new restaurant yet.",
      "options": ["hasn't", "haven't"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense negative statement for the subject 'They' is 'They haven't been to the new restaurant yet.'",
      "correctAnswer": "haven't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ you ever been to Europe?",
      "options": ["Have", "Has"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense question for the subject 'you' is 'Have you ever been to Europe?'",
      "correctAnswer": "Have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ not been feeling well lately.",
      "options": ["hasn't", "haven't"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense negative statement for the subject 'He' is 'He hasn't been feeling well lately.'",
      "correctAnswer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ she been to that concert before?",
      "options": ["Has", "Have"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense question for the subject 'she' is 'Has she been to that concert before?'",
      "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "We ____ not been able to reach the manager.",
      "options": ["hasn't", "haven't"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense negative statement for the subject 'We' is 'We haven't been able to reach the manager.'",
      "correctAnswer": "haven't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be- Perefect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ they ever visited that museum?",
      "options": ["Have", "Has"],
      "explanation": "The correct perfect tense question for the subject 'they' is 'Have they ever visited that museum?'",
      "correctAnswer": "Have"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be + adjective လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She seems ____ today.",
      "options": ["happy", "tall", "running", "delicious"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'happy'.",
      "correctAnswer": "happy"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The cake looks ____.",
      "options": ["blue", "beautiful", "jumping", "loud"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'beautiful'.",
      "correctAnswer": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They are feeling ____ after the vacation.",
      "options": ["sleepy", "small", "reading", "fast"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'sleepy'.",
      "correctAnswer": "sleepy"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The movie was ____.",
      "options": ["quiet", "hot", "sad", "singing"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'sad'.",
      "correctAnswer": "sad"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "This coffee tastes ____.",
      "options": ["yellow", "big", "barking", "bitter"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'bitter'.",
      "correctAnswer": "bitter"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The mountains appear ____ in the distance.",
      "options": ["loud", "friendly", "cold", "dancing"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'cold'.",
      "correctAnswer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "He feels ____ after his workout.",
      "options": ["green", "strong", "happy", "singing"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'strong'.",
      "correctAnswer": "strong"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The dog seems ____ around new people.",
      "options": ["shiny", "friendly", "loud", "slow"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'friendly'.",
      "correctAnswer": "friendly"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The weather is getting ____.",
      "options": ["happy", "hot", "tall", "singing"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'hot'.",
      "correctAnswer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The flowers smell ____ in the garden.",
      "options": ["purple", "beautiful", "running", "loud"],
      "explanation": "The correct adjective to complete the sentence is 'beautiful'.",
      "correctAnswer": "beautiful"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ very excited about the upcoming trip.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The weather ____ quite chilly today.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The weather' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "They ____ very tired after the long hike.",
      "options": ["are", "is", "was", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'They' is 'are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ quite entertaining.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The movie' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "I ____ not sure about this decision.",
      "options": ["am", "is", "was", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'I' is 'am'.",
      "correctAnswer": "am"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The flowers ____ in full bloom during spring.",
      "options": ["are", "is", "was", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The flowers' is 'are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The food ____ delicious at the restaurant.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The food' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ not happy with the exam results.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'She' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The sky ____ clear and sunny today.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The sky' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + adjective  လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The new project ____ quite challenging.",
      "options": ["is", "was", "are", "will be"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' for the subject 'The new project' is 'is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "She ____ very excited about the upcoming trip. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "am not", "aren't", "wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the weather chilly today? (question)",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Am", "Aren't", "Wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "They ____ very tired after the long hike. (negative question)",
      "options": ["aren't", "isn't", "am not", "wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative question is 'aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the movie quite entertaining? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are", "Was"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "I ____ sure about this decision. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["aren't", "am not", "isn't", "wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'am not'.",
      "correctAnswer": "am not"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the flowers in full bloom during spring? (question)",
      "options": ["Are", "Is", "Aren't", "Was"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The food ____ delicious at the restaurant. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not", "wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ she happy with the exam results? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are", "Was"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the sky clear and sunny today? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are", "Was"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Adjective - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The new project ____ quite challenging. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not", "wasn't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition",
      "questionText": "The book is ____ the table.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The cat is ____ the sofa.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The keys are ____ the table.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The pen is ____ the notebook.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'in'.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The car is ____ the garage.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'in'.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The backpack is ____ the chair.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The ball is ____ the box.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'in'.",
      "correctAnswer": "in"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The shoes are ____ the door.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'by'.",
      "correctAnswer": "by"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The glasses are ____ the kitchen counter.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The gift is ____ the table.",
      "options": ["in", "on", "at", "under"],
      "explanation": "The correct preposition to complete the sentence is 'on'.",
      "correctAnswer": "on"
    },

    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The book ____ on the table. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "am not", "aren't"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the cat on the sofa? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The keys ____ under the table. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the pen in the notebook? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The car ____ at the garage. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the backpack on the chair? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The ball ____ under the box. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the shoes by the door? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The glasses ____ on the kitchen counter. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the gift on the table? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The laptop ____ in the bag. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the keys under the book? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The shoes ____ beside the bed. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "____ the phone on the desk? (question)",
      "options": ["Is", "Isn't", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the question is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Be + Preposition - Short Forms",
      "questionText": "The painting ____ above the fireplace. (negative statement)",
      "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "am not"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form of the negative statement is 'isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },

      {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a park near your house?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any milk in the refrigerator?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there many people at the party?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a new movie playing tonight?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there anything I can help you with?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there many books on the shelf?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a good restaurant in this neighborhood?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any interesting events happening this weekend?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a problem with the computer?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Is'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There + am/is/are လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there enough chairs for everyone?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
      "explanation": "The correct form of the verb 'to be' to use with 'there' is 'Are'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },


    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a problem at the office yesterday?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Was' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there any messages for me when I was away?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Were' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a lot of people at the event last night?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Were' when referring to plural objects or people.",
      "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there any problems with the computer system this morning?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Were' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a delay in the train schedule?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Was' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a storm last night?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Was' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there many options for dinner on the menu?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Were' when referring to plural objects or options.",
      "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a fire drill earlier today?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Was' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there any difficulties during the presentation?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Were' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
      "category": "There Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ there a sale at the store yesterday?",
      "options": ["Was", "Were"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Was' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },

    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any problems with the new software?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any updates on the project?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a need for additional resources?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Is not' → 'Isn't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Isn't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any available appointments for today?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any issues with the website?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any missing files from the folder?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any changes to the schedule?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a meeting tomorrow?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Will not be' → 'Won't be'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Won't be"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any concerns about the new policy?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + short form လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there enough chairs for the conference?",
      "options": ["Isn't", "Aren't", "Weren't", "Won't be"],
      "explanation": "The correct short form to use in the question is 'Are not' → 'Aren't'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Aren't"
    },

    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a book on the shelf?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Is' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any apples in the basket?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Are' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a pen on the desk?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Is' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any chairs in the room?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Are' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a cat under the table?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Is' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any papers on the desk?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Are' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a laptop in the bag?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Is' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any flowers in the garden?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Are' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there a TV on the wall?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Is' when referring to a singular subject.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
      "category": "There be + preposition လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ there any shoes by the door?",
      "options": ["Is", "Are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use with 'there' is 'Are' when referring to plural objects or things.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },

    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is your favorite actor?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Who'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Who"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ are you going tonight?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is that delicious smell coming from?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'What'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ are they meeting for lunch?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is your sister studying?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ are you planning to go for vacation?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is that beautiful painting hanging?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ are your friends from?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is your favorite restaurant?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'What'.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions(am/is/are) လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ is teaching the new class?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Who'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Who"
    },

    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was your favorite teacher?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Who'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Who"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ were you last night?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was that loud noise coming from?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'What'.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ were they during the summer vacation?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was your last holiday destination?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ were you planning to visit?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was that old photograph taken?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ were your friends last night?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Where'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was your favorite book as a child?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'What'.",
      "correctAnswer": "What"
    },
    {
      "category": "Wh-Questions with Was/Were",
      "questionText": "____ was leading the team last season?",
      "options": ["Who", "What", "Where"],
      "explanation": "The correct wh-word to use for the question is 'Who'.",
      "correctAnswer": "Who"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ to the gym every morning.",
      "options": ["goes", "go"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'goes' when referring to 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "goes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ soccer on weekends.",
      "options": ["play", "plays"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'play' when referring to 'they'.",
      "correctAnswer": "play"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "I ____ coffee in the morning.",
      "options": ["drink", "drinks"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'drink' when referring to 'I'.",
      "correctAnswer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "My parents ____ a vacation every year.",
      "options": ["take", "takes"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'take' when referring to 'parents'.",
      "correctAnswer": "take"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "____ you enjoy reading science fiction?",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'Do' when forming a question.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ a lot of time on her hobbies.",
      "options": ["spends", "spend"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'spends' when referring to 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "spends"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "He ____ up early for work.",
      "options": ["gets", "get"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'gets' when referring to 'he'.",
      "correctAnswer": "gets"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "____ they usually visit their grandparents?",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'Do' when forming a question.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "We ____ a movie every Friday night.",
      "options": ["watch", "watches"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'watch' when referring to 'we'.",
      "correctAnswer": "watch"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ her dog for a walk in the park.",
      "options": ["takes", "take"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'takes' when referring to 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "takes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "____ he listen to music before going to bed?",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'Does' when forming a question.",
      "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ breakfast together every morning.",
      "options": ["have", "has"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'have' when referring to 'they'.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "I ____ tennis with my friends on Saturdays.",
      "options": ["play", "plays"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'play' when referring to 'I'.",
      "correctAnswer": "play"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ her phone everywhere she goes.",
      "options": ["takes", "take"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'takes' when referring to 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "takes"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "____ they like to travel during the holidays?",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form to use is 'Do' when forming a question.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ tennis on Sundays. (negative)",
      "options": ["don't play", "doesn't play"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'doesn't play' for negative sentences with 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "doesn't play"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ they enjoy hiking? (question)",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'Do' for forming questions.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ you usually eat vegetables? (question)",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'Do' for forming questions.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ his homework in the evening. (negative)",
      "options": ["don't do", "doesn't do"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'doesn't do' for negative sentences with 'he'.",
      "correctAnswer": "doesn't do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ she always arrive on time? (question)",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'Does' for forming questions.",
      "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ coffee in the evening. (negative)",
      "options": ["don't drink", "doesn't drink"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'don't drink' for negative sentences with 'they'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't drink"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ he like watching movies? (question)",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'Does' for forming questions.",
      "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ their dog to the park. (negative)",
      "options": ["don't take", "doesn't take"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'don't take' for negative sentences with 'they'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't take"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ you often go swimming? (question)",
      "options": ["Do", "Does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'Do' for forming questions.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ to the gym in the afternoon. (negative)",
      "options": ["don't go", "doesn't go"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'doesn't go' for negative sentences with 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "doesn't go"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ you study English?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'you'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ she get to work?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'does' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ they celebrate birthdays?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'they'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ he make such delicious food?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'does' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'he'.",
      "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ you usually spend weekends?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'you'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ the dog react to strangers?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'does' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'the dog'.",
      "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ your parents commute to work?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'your parents'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ you handle stress?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'you'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ she manage her time effectively?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'does' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Simple Tense -လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "How ____ you cope with challenges?",
      "options": ["do", "does"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'do' for asking questions in the present simple tense with 'you'.",
      "correctAnswer": "do"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ doing her homework.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'is' for the subject 'she' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ playing soccer in the park.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'are' for the subject 'they' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "I ____ studying for my exams.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'am' for the subject 'I' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "am"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "What ____ you doing this weekend?",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'are' for asking about 'you' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "He ____ reading a book at the moment.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'is' for the subject 'he' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Why ____ she crying?",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'is' for asking about 'she' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ not listening to the teacher.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'are' for the subject 'they' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "I ____ not watching TV right now.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'am' for the subject 'I' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "am"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "What ____ you guys working on?",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'are' for asking about 'you guys' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ not feeling well.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "explanation": "The correct form is 'is' for the subject 'she' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
  
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ (read) a book right now.",
      "options": ["am reading", "is reading", "are reading"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is reading' for the subject 'she' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ (play) soccer at the moment.",
      "options": ["am playing", "is playing", "are playing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are playing' for the subject 'they' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "I ____ (study) for my exams right now.",
      "options": ["am studying", "is studying", "are studying"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'am studying' for the subject 'I' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "am studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "What ____ (you/do) this weekend?",
      "options": ["am doing", "is doing", "are doing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are doing' for the subject 'you' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are doing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ (read) a book at the moment.",
      "options": ["am reading", "is reading", "are reading"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is reading' for the subject 'he' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Why ____ (she/cry)?",
      "options": ["am crying", "is crying", "are crying"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is crying' for the subject 'she' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is crying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ not (listen) to the teacher.",
      "options": ["am not listening", "is not listening", "are not listening"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are not listening' for the subject 'they' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are not listening"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "I ____ not (watch) TV right now.",
      "options": ["am not watching", "is not watching", "are not watching"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'am not watching' for the subject 'I' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "am not watching"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "What ____ (you guys/do)?",
      "options": ["am doing", "is doing", "are doing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are doing' for the subject 'you guys' in the present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are doing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ not (feel) well.",
      "options": ["am not feeling", "is not feeling", "are not feeling"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is not feeling' for the subject 'she' in the negative present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is not feeling"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "She ____ (read) a book right now.",
      "options": ["I'm reading", "She's reading", "You're reading"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'She's reading' using the short form of 'is' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "She's reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "They ____ (play) soccer at the moment.",
      "options": ["You're playing", "They're playing", "He's playing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'They're playing' using the short form of 'are' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "They're playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "I ____ (study) for my exams right now.",
      "options": ["We're studying", "I'm studying", "She's studying"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'I'm studying' using the short form of 'am' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "I'm studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "What ____ (you/do) this weekend?",
      "options": ["We're doing", "You're doing", "He's doing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'You're doing' using the short form of 'are' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "You're doing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "He ____ (read) a book at the moment.",
      "options": ["She's reading", "He's reading", "I'm reading"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'He's reading' using the short form of 'is' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "He's reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Why ____ (she/cry)?",
      "options": ["She's crying", "We're crying", "They're crying"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'She's crying' using the short form of 'is' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "She's crying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "They ____ not (listen) to the teacher.",
      "options": ["We're not listening", "They're not listening", "You're not listening"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'They're not listening' using the short form of 'are not' in the negative form.",
      "correctAnswer": "They're not listening"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "I ____ not (watch) TV right now.",
      "options": ["You're not watching", "I'm not watching", "She's not watching"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'I'm not watching' using the short form of 'am not' in the negative form.",
      "correctAnswer": "I'm not watching"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "What ____ (you guys/do)?",
      "options": ["They're doing", "You're doing", "We're doing"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'You're doing' using the short form of 'are' in the positive form.",
      "correctAnswer": "You're doing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "She ____ not (feel) well.",
      "options": ["I'm not feeling", "She's not feeling", "You're not feeling"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'She's not feeling' using the short form of 'is not' in the negative form.",
      "correctAnswer": "She's not feeling"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (finish) her homework.",
      "options": ["has finish", "have finished", "has finished"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has finished' for the subject 'she' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (visit) three different countries this year.",
      "options": ["has visited", "have visited", "have visit"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have visited' for the subject 'they' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (never/try) sushi before.",
      "options": ["has never tried", "have never tried", "have never try"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have never tried' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have never tried"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What ____ you ____ (do) so far today?",
      "options": ["has done", "have done", "has do"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have done' for 'you' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have done"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (write) two books in his career.",
      "options": ["has write", "have written", "has written"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has written' for the subject 'he' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has written"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Why ____ she ____ (not/finish) her assignment?",
      "options": ["has not finished", "have not finished", "has not finish"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has not finished' for the subject 'she' in the negative present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has not finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (just/arrive) at the airport.",
      "options": ["has just arrived", "have just arrived", "has just arrive"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have just arrived' for the subject 'they' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have just arrived"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (read) that book already.",
      "options": ["has read", "have read", "have reads"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have read' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "How many times ____ you ____ (visit) this museum?",
      "options": ["has visited", "have visited", "have visit"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have you visited' for 'you' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not/eat) lunch yet.",
      "options": ["has not eaten", "have not eaten", "has not eat"],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has not eaten' for the subject 'she' in the negative present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has not eaten"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (visit) Paris twice in her life.",
      "options": [
        "has visit",
        "have visited",
        "has visited",
        "hasn't visited",
        "Has she visited?",
        "Hasn't she visited?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has visited' for the subject 'she' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (already/eat) dinner.",
      "options": [
        "has already eaten",
        "have already eaten",
        "has already eat",
        "haven't eaten",
        "Have they eaten?",
        "Haven't they eaten?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have already eaten' for the subject 'they' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have already eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (never/see) such a beautiful sunset before.",
      "options": [
        "has never seen",
        "have never seen",
        "have never see",
        "haven't seen",
        "Have I seen?",
        "Haven't I seen?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have never seen' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have never seen"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "What ____ you ____ (just/do)?",
      "options": [
        "has just done",
        "have just done",
        "has just do",
        "haven't done",
        "Have you done?",
        "Haven't you done?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have just done' for 'you' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have just done"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (travel) to five different countries so far.",
      "options": [
        "has travel",
        "have traveled",
        "has traveled",
        "hasn't traveled",
        "Has he traveled?",
        "Hasn't he traveled?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has traveled' for the subject 'he' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has traveled"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Why ____ she ____ (not/try) the new restaurant yet?",
      "options": [
        "has not tried",
        "have not tried",
        "has not try",
        "hasn't tried",
        "Has she tried?",
        "Hasn't she tried?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has not tried' for the subject 'she' in the negative present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has not tried"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (not/finish) their project.",
      "options": [
        "has not finished",
        "have not finished",
        "have not finish",
        "haven't finished",
        "Have they finished?",
        "Haven't they finished?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have not finished' for the subject 'they' in the negative present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have not finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (read) all the books in that series.",
      "options": [
        "has read",
        "have read",
        "have reads",
        "haven't read",
        "Have I read?",
        "Haven't I read?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have read' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "How many times ____ you ____ (visit) this museum?",
      "options": [
        "has visited",
        "have visited",
        "have visit",
        "haven't visited",
        "Have you visited?",
        "Haven't you visited?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have you visited' for 'you' in the present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not/read) that book yet.",
      "options": [
        "has not read",
        "have not read",
        "has not reads",
        "hasn't read",
        "Has she read?",
        "Hasn't she read?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has not read' for the subject 'she' in the negative present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has not read"
    },

    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (study) for her exams since morning.",
      "options": [
        "has study",
        "have been studying",
        "has been studying",
        "have studying"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has been studying' for the subject 'she' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (play) football for two hours.",
      "options": [
        "has play",
        "have play",
        "has been playing",
        "have been playing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have been playing' for the subject 'they' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (wait) at the bus stop for 30 minutes.",
      "options": [
        "has been waiting",
        "have been waiting",
        "has waiting",
        "have wait"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have been waiting' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "What ____ you ____ (do) all morning?",
      "options": [
        "has do",
        "have been doing",
        "has been doing",
        "have doing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have been doing' for 'you' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been doing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (work) on the project since last week.",
      "options": [
        "has work",
        "have work",
        "has been working",
        "have been working"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has been working' for the subject 'he' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Why ____ she ____ (not/study) lately?",
      "options": [
        "has not studying",
        "have not studying",
        "has not been studying",
        "have not been studying"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has not been studying' for the subject 'she' in the negative present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has not been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (travel) around Europe for the past two months.",
      "options": [
        "has travel",
        "have travel",
        "has been traveling",
        "have been traveling"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have been traveling' for the subject 'they' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been traveling"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (paint) the house all day long.",
      "options": [
        "has been painting",
        "have been painting",
        "has painting",
        "have painting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have been painting' for the subject 'I' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been painting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "How long ____ you ____ (learn) French?",
      "options": [
        "has learn",
        "have learn",
        "have been learning",
        "has been learning"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have you been learning' for 'you' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have you been learning"
    },
    {
      "category": "Present Perfect Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (practice) the piano since morning.",
      "options": [
        "has practice",
        "have been practicing",
        "has been practicing",
        "have practicing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has been practicing' for the subject 'she' in the present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been practicing"
    },

    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (visit) Paris last summer.",
      "options": [
        "visits",
        "visited",
        "visit",
        "visiting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'visited' for the subject 'she' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (watch) a movie yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "watches",
        "watching",
        "watched",
        "watch"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'watched' for the subject 'they' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (play) soccer with his friends on Saturday.",
      "options": [
        "plays",
        "played",
        "play",
        "playing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'played' for the subject 'he' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "played"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Yesterday, she ____ (read) a book for hours.",
      "options": [
        "reads",
        "reading",
        "read",
        "readed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'read' for the subject 'she' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (visit) the museum last week.",
      "options": [
        "visit",
        "visiting",
        "visited",
        "visits"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'visited' for the subject 'they' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (eat) pizza for dinner yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "eats",
        "ate",
        "eat",
        "eating"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'ate' for the subject 'I' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "ate"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (write) a letter last night.",
      "options": [
        "writes",
        "wrote",
        "writing",
        "writed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wrote' for the subject 'he' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wrote"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "We ____ (go) to the beach on Saturday.",
      "options": [
        "go",
        "goes",
        "went",
        "going"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'went' for the subject 'we' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "went"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (dance) at the party last night.",
      "options": [
        "danced",
        "dances",
        "dance",
        "dancing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'danced' for the subject 'she' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "danced"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Yesterday, he ____ (clean) his room.",
      "options": [
        "cleans",
        "cleaned",
        "clean",
        "cleaning"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'cleaned' for the subject 'he' in the simple past tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "cleaned"
    },

    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (visit) Paris last summer.",
      "options": [
        "didn't visit",
        "visit",
        "visits",
        "Did she visit?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't visit' for the negative form and 'Did she visit?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't visit"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (watch) a movie yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "didn't watch",
        "watched",
        "watches",
        "Did they watch?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't watch' for the negative form and 'Did they watch?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't watch"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (play) soccer with his friends on Saturday.",
      "options": [
        "didn't play",
        "play",
        "plays",
        "Did he play?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't play' for the negative form and 'Did he play?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't play"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Yesterday, she ____ (read) a book for hours.",
      "options": [
        "didn't read",
        "read",
        "reads",
        "Did she read?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't read' for the negative form and 'Did she read?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "They ____ (visit) the museum last week.",
      "options": [
        "didn't visit",
        "visited",
        "visit",
        "Did they visit?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't visit' for the negative form and 'Did they visit?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't visit"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "I ____ (eat) pizza for dinner yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "didn't eat",
        "ate",
        "eats",
        "Did I eat?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't eat' for the negative form and 'Did I eat?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't eat"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "He ____ (write) a letter last night.",
      "options": [
        "didn't write",
        "wrote",
        "writes",
        "Did he write?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't write' for the negative form and 'Did he write?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't write"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "We ____ (go) to the beach on Saturday.",
      "options": [
        "didn't go",
        "went",
        "go",
        "Did we go?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't go' for the negative form and 'Did we go?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't go"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "She ____ (dance) at the party last night.",
      "options": [
        "didn't dance",
        "dance",
        "danced",
        "Did she dance?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't dance' for the negative form and 'Did she dance?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't dance"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Past Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "Yesterday, he ____ (clean) his room.",
      "options": [
        "didn't clean",
        "clean",
        "cleaned",
        "Did he clean?"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answers are 'didn't clean' for the negative form and 'Did he clean?' for the interrogative form in the past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "didn't clean"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "She ____ (watch) TV when I called her.",
      "options": [
        "watching",
        "watched",
        "was watching",
        "did watch"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was watching' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was watching"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "They ____ (play) football yesterday afternoon.",
      "options": [
        "played",
        "were play",
        "were playing",
        "plays"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were playing' for the subject 'they' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "He ____ (work) on his project last night.",
      "options": [
        "working",
        "works",
        "worked",
        "was working"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was working' for the subject 'he' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "While we ____ (have) dinner, it started raining.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "had",
        "was having",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were having' for the subject 'we' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were having"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "She ____ (read) a book at that time.",
      "options": [
        "read",
        "was reading",
        "reads",
        "reading"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was reading' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "I ____ (cook) dinner while you were out.",
      "options": [
        "cooked",
        "was cook",
        "was cooking",
        "cooking"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was cooking' for the subject 'I' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was cooking"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "They ____ (travel) when the storm hit.",
      "options": [
        "traveled",
        "was travel",
        "were traveling",
        "traveling"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were traveling' for the subject 'they' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were traveling"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "We ____ (play) games last evening.",
      "options": [
        "played",
        "was play",
        "were playing",
        "plays"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were playing' for the subject 'we' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "She ____ (dance) at the party when I arrived.",
      "options": [
        "danced",
        "was dance",
        "was dancing",
        "dancing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was dancing' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was dancing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense",
      "questionText": "While he ____ (study), his phone rang.",
      "options": [
        "studied",
        "was study",
        "was studying",
        "studying"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was studying' for the subject 'he' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was studying"
    },

    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ (watch) TV when I called her.",
      "options": [
        "watching",
        "wasn't watching",
        "was watch",
        "didn't watch"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't watching' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't watching"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ (play) football yesterday afternoon.",
      "options": [
        "played",
        "weren't play",
        "were play",
        "didn't play"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'weren't playing' for the subject 'they' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "weren't playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ (work) on his project last night.",
      "options": [
        "working",
        "wasn't working",
        "was work",
        "didn't work"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't working' for the subject 'he' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "While we ____ (have) dinner, it started raining.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "hadn't",
        "weren't having",
        "didn't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'weren't having' for the subject 'we' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "weren't having"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ (read) a book at that time.",
      "options": [
        "read",
        "wasn't reading",
        "was read",
        "didn't read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't reading' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "I ____ (cook) dinner while you were out.",
      "options": [
        "cooking",
        "wasn't cooking",
        "was cook",
        "didn't cook"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't cooking' for the subject 'I' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't cooking"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ (travel) when the storm hit.",
      "options": [
        "traveled",
        "weren't travel",
        "were traveling",
        "didn't travel"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'weren't traveling' for the subject 'they' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "weren't traveling"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "We ____ (play) games last evening.",
      "options": [
        "played",
        "weren't play",
        "were playing",
        "didn't play"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'weren't playing' for the subject 'we' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "weren't playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ (dance) at the party when I arrived.",
      "options": [
        "danced",
        "wasn't dancing",
        "was dance",
        "didn't dance"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't dancing' for the subject 'she' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't dancing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "While he ____ (study), his phone rang.",
      "options": [
        "studied",
        "wasn't studying",
        "was study",
        "didn't study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'wasn't studying' for the subject 'he' in the past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "wasn't studying"
    },

    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "By the time I arrived, they ____ (already eat).",
      "options": [
        "already ate",
        "already eaten",
        "ate"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had already eaten' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "already eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "She ____ (finish) her work before the meeting started.",
      "options": [
        "finished",
        "had finished",
        "finish"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had finished' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "When he arrived, they ____ (leave) already.",
      "options": [
        "had already leave",
        "had already left",
        "already left"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had already left' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had already left"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "I realized I ____ (forget) my keys at home.",
      "options": [
        "had forget",
        "had forgotten",
        "forgot"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had forgotten' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had forgotten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "She told me she ____ (already watch) the movie.",
      "options": [
        "already watched",
        "had watched",
        "watched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had already watched' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "already watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "He wasn't hungry because he ____ (just eat).",
      "options": [
        "had just eat",
        "had just eaten",
        "just ate"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had just eaten' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had just eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "By the time they arrived, the concert ____ (start).",
      "options": [
        "already started",
        "had already started",
        "started"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had already started' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had already started"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "She told me she ____ (never be) to Japan before.",
      "options": [
        "never was",
        "had never been",
        "never been"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had never been' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had never been"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "After I had finished the book, I ____ (return) it to the library.",
      "options": [
        "returned",
        "had returned",
        "return"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had returned' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had returned"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 1",
      "questionText": "He realized he ____ (lose) his wallet.",
      "options": [
        "had lose",
        "had lost",
        "lost"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had lost' in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had lost"
    },

    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not finish) her homework before the teacher asked.",
      "options": [
        "hadn't finished",
        "didn't finish"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hadn't finished' for the negative sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "Had they ____ (already leave) when you arrived?",
      "options": [
        "already left",
        "left"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'already left' for the question sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "already left"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "He ____ (not eat) breakfast before he went to the gym.",
      "options": [
        "hadn't eaten",
        "didn't eat"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hadn't eaten' for the negative sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "Had she ____ (read) the book before the movie started?",
      "options": [
        "read",
        "already read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'read' for the question sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "They ____ (not arrive) at the airport when the flight left.",
      "options": [
        "hadn't arrived",
        "didn't arrive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hadn't arrived' for the negative sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't arrived"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "Had you ____ (ever visit) that museum before?",
      "options": [
        "ever visited",
        "visited"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'ever visited' for the question sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "ever visited"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "He ____ (not tell) anyone about the surprise party.",
      "options": [
        "hadn't told",
        "didn't tell"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hadn't told' for the negative sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't told"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "Had she ____ (finish) her project when the deadline passed?",
      "options": [
        "finish",
        "finished"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'finished' for the question sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "They ____ (not watch) the movie before it got dark.",
      "options": [
        "hadn't watched",
        "didn't watch"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hadn't watched' for the negative sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Tense Exercise 2",
      "questionText": "Had he ____ (visit) that place previously?",
      "options": [
        "visited",
        "ever visited"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'ever visited' for the question sentence in the past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "ever visited"
    },

    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (study) for hours before the exam.",
      "options": [
        "had been studying",
        "was studying",
        "studied"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been studying' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "Had they ____ (wait) for a long time?",
      "options": [
        "waited",
        "had been waiting",
        "were waiting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been waiting' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "He realized he ____ (run) for an hour.",
      "options": [
        "had been running",
        "was running",
        "had run"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been running' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been running"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "Had she ____ (practice) before the performance?",
      "options": [
        "had been practicing",
        "had practiced",
        "practiced"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been practicing' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been practicing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time they arrived, the team ____ (train) for two hours.",
      "options": [
        "had been training",
        "was training",
        "had trained"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been training' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been training"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She was tired because she ____ (work) all day.",
      "options": [
        "had been working",
        "was working",
        "had worked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been working' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "Had you ____ (wait) for a while before I arrived?",
      "options": [
        "had been waiting",
        "were waiting",
        "waited"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been waiting' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "They were exhausted because they ____ (run) a marathon.",
      "options": [
        "had been running",
        "were running",
        "had run"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been running' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been running"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "Had he ____ (read) the book before the movie started?",
      "options": [
        "had been reading",
        "was reading",
        "had read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been reading' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been reading"
    },
    {
      "category": "Past Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I realized I ____ (wait) for the bus for half an hour.",
      "options": [
        "had been waiting",
        "was waiting",
        "had waited"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'had been waiting' in the past perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been waiting"
    },

    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (visit) her grandmother tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "will visit",
        "visits"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will visit' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will visit"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not be) at the party this weekend.",
      "options": [
        "will not be",
        "am not"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not be' for 'will not be' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not be"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ he ____ (call) you later?",
      "options": [
        "Will he call",
        "Does he call"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will he call' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will he call"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "We ____ (have) a meeting next week.",
      "options": [
        "will have",
        "have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not forget) to bring the documents.",
      "options": [
        "will not forget",
        "does not forget"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not forget' for 'will not forget' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not forget"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ they ____ (attend) the conference?",
      "options": [
        "Will they attend",
        "Do they attend"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will they attend' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will they attend"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "He ____ (go) to the gym after work.",
      "options": [
        "will go",
        "goes"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will go' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will go"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not eat) fast food anymore.",
      "options": [
        "will not eat",
        "do not eat"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not eat' for 'will not eat' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not eat"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ she ____ (get) the job?",
      "options": [
        "Will she get",
        "Does she get"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will she get' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will she get"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "They ____ (travel) to Paris next month.",
      "options": [
        "will travel",
        "travel"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will travel' in the simple future tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will travel"
    },

    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not go) to the party tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "won't go",
        "will not go"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'won't go' for 'will not go' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "won't go"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "I think they ____ (be) there.",
      "options": [
        "won't be",
        "will not be"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'won't be' for 'will not be' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "won't be"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ they ____ (come) to the event?",
      "options": [
        "Will, come",
        "Will, comes"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will they come' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, come"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not forget) to call you.",
      "options": [
        "won't forget",
        "will not forget"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'won't forget' for 'will not forget' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "won't forget"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "He ____ (arrive) on time.",
      "options": [
        "will arrive",
        "will arrives"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will arrive' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "will arrive"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "They ____ (not help) with the project.",
      "options": [
        "won't help",
        "will not help"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'won't help' for 'will not help' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "won't help"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ you ____ (meet) him tomorrow?",
      "options": [
        "Will, meet",
        "Will, meets"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will you meet' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, meet"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (finish) the project in time.",
      "options": [
        "will finish",
        "will finishes"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will finish' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "will finish"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not see) him at the party.",
      "options": [
        "won't see",
        "will not see"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'won't see' for 'will not see' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "won't see"
    },
    {
      "category": "Simple Future Tense Short Form Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ we ____ (get) the results soon?",
      "options": [
        "Will, get",
        "Will, gets"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will we get' in short form.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, get"
    },


    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (study) all night tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "will be studying",
        "will study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will be studying' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I think they ____ (work) on the project at this time next week.",
      "options": [
        "will be working",
        "will work"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will be working' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ he ____ (travel) to Europe in July?",
      "options": [
        "Will, be traveling",
        "Will, travel"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will he be traveling' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, be traveling"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "We ____ (wait) for you at the airport.",
      "options": [
        "will be waiting",
        "will wait"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will be waiting' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (not cook) dinner at 6 PM.",
      "options": [
        "will not be cooking",
        "will not cook"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not be cooking' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not be cooking"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ they ____ (watch) a movie later?",
      "options": [
        "Will, be watching",
        "Will, watch"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will they be watching' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, be watching"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "He ____ (work) at the office tomorrow afternoon.",
      "options": [
        "will be working",
        "will work"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will be working' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not sleep) at this time next week.",
      "options": [
        "will not be sleeping",
        "will not sleep"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not be sleeping' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not be sleeping"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ she ____ (practice) the piano later?",
      "options": [
        "Will, be practicing",
        "Will, practice"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will she be practicing' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, be practicing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "They ____ (study) for the exam at this time tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "will be studying",
        "will study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will be studying' in the future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be studying"
    },


    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time he arrives, we ____ (finish) the presentation.",
      "options": [
        "will have finished",
        "will finish"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have finished' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I think she ____ (complete) the project by tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "will have completed",
        "will complete"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have completed' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ you ____ (arrive) at the airport by 5 PM?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have arrived",
        "Will, arrive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will you have arrived' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have arrived"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (read) the book by the end of the month.",
      "options": [
        "will have read",
        "will read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have read' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not forget) to send the email by the time you arrive.",
      "options": [
        "will not have forgotten",
        "will not forget"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not have forgotten' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not have forgotten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ they ____ (meet) the deadline by tomorrow?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have met",
        "Will, meet"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will they have met' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have met"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "He ____ (already finish) his homework by the time the teacher collects it.",
      "options": [
        "will have already finished",
        "will already finish"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have already finished' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have already finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (not find) my keys by the time I need to leave.",
      "options": [
        "will not have found",
        "will not find"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will not have found' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will not have found"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ she ____ (learn) the song by the concert?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have learned",
        "Will, learn"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will she have learned' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have learned"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "They ____ (already finish) the project by the time the boss arrives.",
      "options": [
        "will have already finished",
        "will already finish"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have already finished' in the future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have already finished"
    },


    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time we arrive, they ____ (wait) for hours.",
      "options": [
        "will have been waiting",
        "will wait"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been waiting' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I think she ____ (study) for the test for a long time.",
      "options": [
        "will have been studying",
        "will study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been studying' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ you ____ (work) on this project all day?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have been working",
        "Will, work"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will you have been working' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have been working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "She ____ (exercise) for two hours by the time you come.",
      "options": [
        "will have been exercising",
        "will exercise"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been exercising' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been exercising"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (study) English for a while before the exam.",
      "options": [
        "will have been studying",
        "will study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been studying' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ they ____ (practice) the dance routine all morning?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have been practicing",
        "Will, practice"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will they have been practicing' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have been practicing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "He ____ (work) for the company since last year.",
      "options": [
        "will have been working",
        "will work"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been working' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "I ____ (wait) for you for hours by the time you arrive.",
      "options": [
        "will have been waiting",
        "will wait"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been waiting' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been waiting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "____ she ____ (study) for the exam for a long time?",
      "options": [
        "Will, have been studying",
        "Will, study"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will she have been studying' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Will, have been studying"
    },
    {
      "category": "Future Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "They ____ (wait) at the restaurant for an hour by the time we arrive.",
      "options": [
        "will have been waiting",
        "will wait"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will have been waiting' in the future perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been waiting"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The book ____ (read) by many students.",
      "options": [
        "is read",
        "reads",
        "has read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is read' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The cake ____ (bake) by my mom every weekend.",
      "options": [
        "is baked",
        "bakes",
        "has baked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is baked' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is baked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "English ____ (speak) in many countries around the world.",
      "options": [
        "is spoken",
        "speaks",
        "has spoken"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is spoken' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is spoken"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (wash) every week.",
      "options": [
        "is washed",
        "washes",
        "has washed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is washed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is washed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Vegetables and fruits ____ (sell) at the local market.",
      "options": [
        "are sold",
        "sell",
        "have sold"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are sold' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are sold"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The news ____ (watch) by millions of people.",
      "options": [
        "is watched",
        "watches",
        "has watched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is watched' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Dinner ____ (cook) by my sister every evening.",
      "options": [
        "is cooked",
        "cooks",
        "has cooked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is cooked' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is cooked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (enjoy) by the audience.",
      "options": [
        "is enjoyed",
        "enjoys",
        "has enjoyed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is enjoyed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is enjoyed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "The emails ____ (send) every day.",
      "options": [
        "are sent",
        "sends",
        "have sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are sent' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁)",
      "questionText": "Homework ____ (complete) by the students.",
      "options": [
        "is completed",
        "completes",
        "has completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is completed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The book ____ (read) by many students.",
      "options": [
        "is read",
        "reads",
        "is not read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is read' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ the cake ____ (bake) by my mom every weekend?",
      "options": [
        "Is, baked",
        "Do, bake",
        "Is, not baked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is the cake baked' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, baked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "English ____ (speak) in many countries around the world.",
      "options": [
        "is spoken",
        "speaks",
        "is not spoken"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is spoken' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is spoken"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (wash) every week.",
      "options": [
        "is washed",
        "washes",
        "is not washed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is washed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is washed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ vegetables and fruits ____ (sell) at the local market?",
      "options": [
        "Are, sold",
        "Do, sell",
        "Are, not sold"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Are vegetables and fruits sold' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are, sold"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ the news ____ (watch) by millions of people?",
      "options": [
        "Is, watched",
        "Do, watch",
        "Is, not watched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is the news watched' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ dinner ____ (cook) by my sister every evening?",
      "options": [
        "Is, cooked",
        "Does, cook",
        "Is, not cooked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is dinner cooked' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, cooked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ the movie ____ (enjoy) by the audience?",
      "options": [
        "Is, enjoyed",
        "Do, enjoy",
        "Is, not enjoyed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is the movie enjoyed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, enjoyed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ the emails ____ (send) every day?",
      "options": [
        "Are, sent",
        "Do, send",
        "Are, not sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Are the emails sent' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are, sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၂)",
      "questionText": "____ homework ____ (complete) by the students?",
      "options": [
        "Is, completed",
        "Do, complete",
        "Is, not completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is homework completed' in the passive voice present simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, completed"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The house ____ (build) by a construction team.",
      "options": [
        "is being built",
        "is building",
        "is not being built"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being built' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being built"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "Right now, a delicious meal ____ (prepare) in the kitchen.",
      "options": [
        "is being prepared",
        "is preparing",
        "is not being prepared"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being prepared' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being prepared"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The garden ____ (water) by the gardener at the moment.",
      "options": [
        "is being watered",
        "is watering",
        "is not being watered"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being watered' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being watered"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The guests ____ (welcome) to the event by the host.",
      "options": [
        "are being welcomed",
        "are welcoming",
        "are not being welcomed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are being welcomed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are being welcomed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "A new bridge ____ (construct) over the river at this very moment.",
      "options": [
        "is being constructed",
        "is constructing",
        "is not being constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being constructed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "A fascinating documentary ____ (film) by a talented director currently.",
      "options": [
        "is being filmed",
        "is filming",
        "is not being filmed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being filmed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being filmed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The guests ____ (entertain) with music and dance.",
      "options": [
        "are being entertained",
        "are entertaining",
        "are not being entertained"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are being entertained' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are being entertained"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The old building ____ (renovate) to give it a fresh look.",
      "options": [
        "is being renovated",
        "is renovating",
        "is not being renovated"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being renovated' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being renovated"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The play ____ (perform) by a talented group of actors tonight.",
      "options": [
        "is being performed",
        "is performing",
        "is not being performed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being performed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being performed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "At the moment, a new fashion collection ____ (present) on the runway.",
      "options": [
        "is being presented",
        "is presenting",
        "is not being presented"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being presented' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being presented"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The project ____ (work on) by a team of skilled professionals.",
      "options": [
        "is being worked on",
        "is working on",
        "is not being worked on"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being worked on' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being worked on"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The computer program ____ (test) to ensure its functionality.",
      "options": [
        "is being tested",
        "is testing",
        "is not being tested"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being tested' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being tested"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "Right now, a new mural ____ (paint) on the city wall.",
      "options": [
        "is being painted",
        "is painting",
        "is not being painted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being painted' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being painted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "A delicious meal ____ (prepare) for the special event.",
      "options": [
        "is being prepared",
        "is preparing",
        "is not being prepared"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being prepared' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being prepared"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၅ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The new skyscraper ____ (construct) by a renowned construction company.",
      "options": [
        "is being constructed",
        "is constructing",
        "is not being constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is being constructed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is being constructed"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "____ the house ____ (build) by a construction team?",
      "options": [
        "Is, being built",
        "Are, building"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is the house being built' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, being built"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The house ____ not ____ (construct) by the owner.",
      "options": [
        "is, being constructed",
        "is not, being constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The house is not being constructed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is not, being constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "____ a new bridge ____ (build) over the river?",
      "options": [
        "Is, being built",
        "Are, building"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is a new bridge being built' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, being built"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "A new bridge ____ not ____ (construct) at the moment.",
      "options": [
        "is, being constructed",
        "is not, being constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'A new bridge is not being constructed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is not, being constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "____ the guests ____ (welcome) to the event?",
      "options": [
        "Are, being welcomed",
        "Is, welcoming"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Are the guests being welcomed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Are, being welcomed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The guests ____ not ____ (entertain) with live music.",
      "options": [
        "are, being entertained",
        "are not, being entertained"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The guests are not being entertained' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "are not, being entertained"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "____ a fascinating documentary ____ (film) right now?",
      "options": [
        "Is, being filmed",
        "Is, filming"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is a fascinating documentary being filmed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, being filmed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "A fascinating documentary ____ not ____ (film) at this moment.",
      "options": [
        "is, being filmed",
        "is not, being filmed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'A fascinating documentary is not being filmed' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is not, being filmed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "____ the old building ____ (renovate) currently?",
      "options": [
        "Is, being renovated",
        "Is, renovating"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Is the old building being renovated' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "Is, being renovated"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Continuous Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း (၁၀ မေးခွန်း)",
      "questionText": "The old building ____ not ____ (renovate) right now.",
      "options": [
        "is, being renovated",
        "is not, being renovated"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The old building is not being renovated' in the passive voice present continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "is not, being renovated"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The new building ____ (complete) by the architect.",
      "options": [
        "has been completed",
        "has completed",
        "has not been completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The new building has been completed' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The project ____ (finish) on time.",
      "options": [
        "has been finished",
        "has finished",
        "has not been finished"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The project has been finished' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The books ____ (publish) by a renowned company.",
      "options": [
        "have been published",
        "have published",
        "have not been published"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The books have been published' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been published"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The repairs ____ (complete) in the morning.",
      "options": [
        "have been completed",
        "have completed",
        "have not been completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The repairs have been completed' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The artwork ____ (display) at the art gallery.",
      "options": [
        "has been displayed",
        "has displayed",
        "has not been displayed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The artwork has been displayed' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been displayed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The secret ____ (reveal) to the public.",
      "options": [
        "has been revealed",
        "has revealed",
        "has not been revealed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The secret has been revealed' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been revealed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The news ____ (announce) on the radio.",
      "options": [
        "has been announced",
        "has announced",
        "has not been announced"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The news has been announced' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been announced"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The documents ____ (submit) to the authorities.",
      "options": [
        "have been submitted",
        "have submitted",
        "have not been submitted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The documents have been submitted' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been submitted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (repair) by the mechanic.",
      "options": [
        "has been repaired",
        "has repaired",
        "has not been repaired"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The car has been repaired' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been repaired"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The report ____ (compile) by the team.",
      "options": [
        "has been compiled",
        "has compiled",
        "has not been compiled"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The report has been compiled' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been compiled"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The tickets ____ (book) for the concert.",
      "options": [
        "have been booked",
        "have booked",
        "have not been booked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The tickets have been booked' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been booked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The message ____ (send) to all employees.",
      "options": [
        "has been sent",
        "has sent",
        "has not been sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The message has been sent' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The event ____ (organize) by the community.",
      "options": [
        "has been organized",
        "has organized",
        "has not been organized"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The event has been organized' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been organized"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The decision ____ (make) by the board of directors.",
      "options": [
        "has been made",
        "has made",
        "has not been made"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The decision has been made' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been made"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Tense လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The problem ____ (solve) by the experts.",
      "options": [
        "has been solved",
        "has solved",
        "has not been solved"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The problem has been solved' in the passive voice present perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been solved"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The garden ____ (be) being watered by the gardener.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The garden has been being watered' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The cake ____ (be) being baked by the chef.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The cake has been being baked' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The project ____ (be) being worked on by the team.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The project has been being worked on' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (be) being repaired at the garage.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The car has been being repaired' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The fields ____ (be) being cultivated by the farmers.",
      "options": [
        "have been",
        "have been being",
        "have not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The fields have been being cultivated' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "have been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The house ____ (be) being painted by the workers.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The house has been being painted' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The new software ____ (be) being developed by the programmers.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The new software has been being developed' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The book ____ (be) being written by the author.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The book has been being written' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The road ____ (be) being repaired by the construction crew.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The road has been being repaired' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Present Perfect Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The event ____ (be) being organized by the volunteers.",
      "options": [
        "has been",
        "has been being",
        "has not been being"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The event has been being organized' in the passive voice present perfect continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "has been being"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The cake ____ (eat) by the children at the party.",
      "options": [
        "was eaten",
        "was enjoyed",
        "was baked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The cake was eaten' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The letter ____ (send) by the post office last week.",
      "options": [
        "was sent",
        "was received",
        "was ignored"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The letter was sent' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The book ____ (write) by a famous author in the 19th century.",
      "options": [
        "was written",
        "was published",
        "was forgotten"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The book was written' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was written"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (watch) by millions of people last weekend.",
      "options": [
        "was watched",
        "was ignored",
        "was criticized"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The movie was watched' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The building ____ (construct) many years ago.",
      "options": [
        "was constructed",
        "was demolished",
        "was abandoned"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The building was constructed' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The song ____ (sing) beautifully by the choir.",
      "options": [
        "was sung",
        "was composed",
        "was shouted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The song was sung' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was sung"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The news ____ (announce) on the radio yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "was announced",
        "was ignored",
        "was distorted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The news was announced' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was announced"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The play ____ (perform) at the theater last night.",
      "options": [
        "was performed",
        "was canceled",
        "was forgotten"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The play was performed' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was performed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The room ____ (clean) by the hotel staff.",
      "options": [
        "was cleaned",
        "was messy",
        "was neglected"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The room was cleaned' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was cleaned"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The party ____ (organize) by a group of friends.",
      "options": [
        "was organized",
        "was canceled",
        "was forgotten"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The party was organized' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was organized"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The letter ____ (send) by Mary yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "was sent",
        "was send",
        "was not sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The letter was sent' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The novel ____ (write) by Mark Twain.",
      "options": [
        "was written",
        "was wrote",
        "was not written"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The novel was written' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was written"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The house ____ (build) in the 19th century.",
      "options": [
        "was built",
        "was build",
        "was not built"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The house was built' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was built"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The painting ____ (create) by a famous artist.",
      "options": [
        "was created",
        "was create",
        "was not created"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The painting was created' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was created"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The homework ____ (do) by the students.",
      "options": [
        "was done",
        "was do",
        "was not done"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The homework was done' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was done"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (watch) by many people.",
      "options": [
        "was watched",
        "was watch",
        "was not watched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The movie was watched' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was watched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The work ____ (complete) last week.",
      "options": [
        "was completed",
        "was complete",
        "was not completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The work was completed' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The book ____ (read) by many people.",
      "options": [
        "was read",
        "was readed",
        "was not read"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The book was read' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was read"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The meal ____ (cook) by a professional chef.",
      "options": [
        "was cooked",
        "was cook",
        "was not cooked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The meal was cooked' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was cooked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Simple လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "The experiment ____ (conduct) in a laboratory.",
      "options": [
        "was conducted",
        "was conduct",
        "was not conducted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The experiment was conducted' in the passive voice past simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was conducted"
    },

  {
    "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
    "questionText": "The cake ____ (bake) by the chef when the power went out.",
    "options": [
      "was being baked",
      "was baking",
      "was not baked"
    ],
    "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The cake was being baked by the chef when the power went out.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
    "correctAnswer": "was being baked"
  },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (repair) at the mechanic's garage last week.",
      "options": [
        "was being repaired",
        "was repaired",
        "was not repaired"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The car was being repaired at the mechanic's garage last week.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being repaired"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The children ____ (play) in the park when it started raining.",
      "options": [
        "were playing",
        "were being played",
        "were not playing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The children were playing in the park when it started raining.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were playing"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The building ____ (construct) while the workers were on strike.",
      "options": [
        "was constructing",
        "was constructed",
        "was being constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The building was being constructed while the workers were on strike.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (film) when the director suddenly fell ill.",
      "options": [
        "was filmed",
        "was being filmed",
        "was not filmed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The movie was being filmed when the director suddenly fell ill.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being filmed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The door ____ (repair) while I was away.",
      "options": [
        "was repairing",
        "was not repairing",
        "was being repaired"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The door was being repaired while I was away.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being repaired"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The scientists ____ (conduct) experiments throughout the night.",
      "options": [
        "were conducting",
        "were being conducted",
        "were not conducting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The scientists were conducting experiments throughout the night.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were conducting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The street ____ (block) due to the construction work.",
      "options": [
        "was blocking",
        "was being blocked",
        "was not blocking"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The street was being blocked due to the construction work.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being blocked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The dinner ____ (prepare) while the guests were arriving.",
      "options": [
        "was preparing",
        "was being prepared",
        "was not preparing"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The dinner was being prepared while the guests were arriving.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "was being prepared"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Continuous လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The trees ____ (plant) in the park last spring.",
      "options": [
        "were planted",
        "were being planted",
        "were not planted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The trees were being planted in the park last spring.' in the passive voice past continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "were being planted"
    },

  
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The report ____ (already submit) by the time I arrived.",
      "options": [
        "had already submitted",
        "had already been submitted",
        "had not already submitted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The report had already been submitted by the time I arrived.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had already been submitted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (not release) when we checked the cinema listings.",
      "options": [
        "had not released",
        "had not been released",
        "hadn't released"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The movie had not been released when we checked the cinema listings.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had not been released"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The repairs ____ (complete) before the customer arrived.",
      "options": [
        "had completed",
        "had been completed",
        "hadn't completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The repairs had been completed before the customer arrived.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The cake ____ (eat) by the time we found it in the kitchen.",
      "options": [
        "had eaten",
        "had been eaten",
        "hadn't eaten"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The cake had been eaten by the time we found it in the kitchen.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been eaten"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The books ____ (return) to the library before the due date.",
      "options": [
        "had returned",
        "had been returned",
        "hadn't returned"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The books had been returned to the library before the due date.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been returned"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The meeting ____ (cancel) because of the sudden storm.",
      "options": [
        "had cancelled",
        "had been cancelled",
        "hadn't cancelled"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The meeting had been cancelled because of the sudden storm.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been cancelled"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The car ____ (repair) by the mechanic before it broke down again.",
      "options": [
        "had repaired",
        "had been repaired",
        "hadn't repaired"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The car had been repaired by the mechanic before it broke down again.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been repaired"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The presentation ____ (prepare) before the projector malfunctioned.",
      "options": [
        "had prepared",
        "had been prepared",
        "hadn't prepared"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The presentation had been prepared before the projector malfunctioned.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been prepared"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The message ____ (send) by the time I checked my email.",
      "options": [
        "had sent",
        "had been sent",
        "hadn't sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The message had been sent by the time I checked my email.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been sent"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Past Perfect လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The tickets ____ (book) before we arrived at the travel agency.",
      "options": [
        "had booked",
        "had been booked",
        "hadn't booked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The tickets had been booked before we arrived at the travel agency.' in the passive voice past perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "had been booked"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The new product ____ (launch) next month.",
      "options": [
        "will launch",
        "will be launched",
        "will not launched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The new product will be launched next month.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be launched"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The conference ____ (hold) in the main auditorium.",
      "options": [
        "will hold",
        "will be held",
        "will not held"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The conference will be held in the main auditorium.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be held"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The package ____ (deliver) to your address tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "will deliver",
        "will be delivered",
        "will not delivered"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The package will be delivered to your address tomorrow.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be delivered"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The party ____ (organize) by my friends next week.",
      "options": [
        "will organize",
        "will be organized",
        "will not organized"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The party will be organized by my friends next week.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be organized"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The report ____ (submit) to the supervisor by Friday.",
      "options": [
        "will submit",
        "will be submitted",
        "will not submitted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The report will be submitted to the supervisor by Friday.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be submitted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The tickets ____ (book) for the concert.",
      "options": [
        "will book",
        "will be booked",
        "will not booked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The tickets will be booked for the concert.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be booked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The construction ____ (complete) in six months.",
      "options": [
        "will complete",
        "will be completed",
        "will not completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The construction will be completed in six months.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ (release) next Friday.",
      "options": [
        "will release",
        "will be released",
        "will not released"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The movie will be released next Friday.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be released"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The event ____ (broadcast) live on television.",
      "options": [
        "will broadcast",
        "will be broadcast",
        "will not broadcast"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The event will be broadcast live on television.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be broadcast"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "The message ____ (send) to all employees.",
      "options": [
        "will send",
        "will be sent",
        "will not sent"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'The message will be sent to all employees.' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be sent"
    },


    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the documents ____ (review) before the meeting?",
      "options": [
        "be reviewed",
        "not be reviewed",
        "will not be reviewed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the documents be reviewed before the meeting?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be reviewed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the concert tickets ____ (sell) online?",
      "options": [
        "be sold",
        "not be sold",
        "will not be sold"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the concert tickets be sold online?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be sold"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the event ____ (cancel) due to bad weather?",
      "options": [
        "be cancelled",
        "not be cancelled",
        "will not be cancelled"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the event be cancelled due to bad weather?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be cancelled"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the project ____ (complete) by the deadline?",
      "options": [
        "be completed",
        "not be completed",
        "will not be completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the project be completed by the deadline?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the awards ____ (present) at the ceremony?",
      "options": [
        "be presented",
        "not be presented",
        "will not be presented"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the awards be presented at the ceremony?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be presented"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the information ____ (share) with the participants?",
      "options": [
        "be shared",
        "not be shared",
        "will not be shared"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the information be shared with the participants?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be shared"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the guests ____ (welcome) by the hotel staff?",
      "options": [
        "be welcomed",
        "not be welcomed",
        "will not be welcomed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the guests be welcomed by the hotel staff?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be welcomed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the instructions ____ (provide) in the user manual?",
      "options": [
        "be provided",
        "not be provided",
        "will not be provided"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the instructions be provided in the user manual?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be provided"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the news ____ (broadcast) on television tonight?",
      "options": [
        "be broadcast",
        "not be broadcast",
        "will not be broadcast"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the news be broadcast on television tonight?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be broadcast"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Simple Tense Exercise (Interrogative/Negative)",
      "questionText": "Will the ceremony ____ (hold) in the main hall?",
      "options": [
        "be held",
        "not be held",
        "will not be held"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Will the ceremony be held in the main hall?' in the passive voice future simple tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "be held"
    },

    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "At this time tomorrow, the project ____ (being work) on by the team.",
      "options": [
        "will being worked",
        "will be being worked",
        "will be worked"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'At this time tomorrow, the project will be being worked on by the team.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being worked"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "During the presentation, the new software ____ (being demonstrate) by the developers.",
      "options": [
        "will being demonstrated",
        "will be being demonstrated",
        "will be demonstrated"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'During the presentation, the new software will be being demonstrated by the developers.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being demonstrated"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By this time next week, the repairs ____ (being complete) on the bridge.",
      "options": [
        "will being completed",
        "will be being completed",
        "will be completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By this time next week, the repairs will be being completed on the bridge.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "In a few hours, the new movie ____ (being screen) at the cinema.",
      "options": [
        "will being screened",
        "will be being screened",
        "will be screened"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'In a few hours, the new movie will be being screened at the cinema.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being screened"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "At this time next month, a special event ____ (being hold) in the park.",
      "options": [
        "will being held",
        "will be being held",
        "will be held"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'At this time next month, a special event will be being held in the park.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being held"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "During the conference, important topics ____ (being discuss) by the participants.",
      "options": [
        "will being discussed",
        "will be being discussed",
        "will be discussed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'During the conference, important topics will be being discussed by the participants.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being discussed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the end of the day, a new design ____ (being finalize) by the team.",
      "options": [
        "will being finalized",
        "will be being finalized",
        "will be finalized"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the end of the day, a new design will be being finalized by the team.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being finalized"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "In a few moments, an important announcement ____ (being make) by the company.",
      "options": [
        "will being made",
        "will be being made",
        "will be made"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'In a few moments, an important announcement will be being made by the company.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being made"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "Tomorrow afternoon, a live webinar ____ (being host) by the experts.",
      "options": [
        "will being hosted",
        "will be being hosted",
        "will be hosted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Tomorrow afternoon, a live webinar will be being hosted by the experts.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being hosted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Continuous Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By this time next year, a new building ____ (being construct) in the city center.",
      "options": [
        "will being constructed",
        "will be being constructed",
        "will be constructed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By this time next year, a new building will be being constructed in the city center.' in the passive voice future continuous tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will be being constructed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the end of the week, all the tasks ____ (be complete).",
      "options": [
        "will be complete",
        "will have complete",
        "will have been completed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the end of the week, all the tasks will have been completed.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been completed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time they arrive, the preparations ____ (be finish).",
      "options": [
        "will be finish",
        "will have finish",
        "will have been finished"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the time they arrive, the preparations will have been finished.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been finished"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By next month, the new regulations ____ (be implement).",
      "options": [
        "will be implement",
        "will have implement",
        "will have been implemented"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By next month, the new regulations will have been implemented.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been implemented"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time the guests arrive, the venue ____ (be decorate).",
      "options": [
        "will be decorate",
        "will have decorate",
        "will have been decorated"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the time the guests arrive, the venue will have been decorated.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been decorated"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the end of the month, the reports ____ (be compile).",
      "options": [
        "will be compile",
        "will have compile",
        "will have been compiled"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the end of the month, the reports will have been compiled.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been compiled"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By next year, the new technology ____ (be adopt) by many companies.",
      "options": [
        "will be adopt",
        "will have adopt",
        "will have been adopted"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By next year, the new technology will have been adopted by many companies.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been adopted"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time the event starts, all the arrangements ____ (be finalize).",
      "options": [
        "will be finalize",
        "will have finalize",
        "will have been finalized"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the time the event starts, all the arrangements will have been finalized.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been finalized"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the end of the day, the progress ____ (be assess) by the team.",
      "options": [
        "will be assess",
        "will have assess",
        "will have been assessed"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the end of the day, the progress will have been assessed by the team.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been assessed"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By the time the results are announced, the winners ____ (be congratulate).",
      "options": [
        "will be congratulate",
        "will have congratulate",
        "will have been congratulated"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By the time the results are announced, the winners will have been congratulated.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been congratulated"
    },
    {
      "category": "Passive Voice Future Perfect Tense Exercise",
      "questionText": "By next week, the new website ____ (be launch) by the company.",
      "options": [
        "will be launch",
        "will have launch",
        "will have been launched"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'By next week, the new website will have been launched by the company.' in the passive voice future perfect tense.",
      "correctAnswer": "will have been launched"
    },

    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He doesn't know what ____.",
      "options": [
        "to do",
        "doing",
        "does"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'to do'. Noun clauses can act as objects of verbs, and in this sentence, 'what to do' is the object of 'know'.",
      "correctAnswer": "to do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She asked where ____.",
      "options": [
        "is the library",
        "was the library",
        "the library is"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'the library is'. Noun clauses can function as direct objects of verbs, and in this sentence, 'where the library is' is the direct object of 'asked'.",
      "correctAnswer": "the library is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I wonder who ____ the game.",
      "options": [
        "will win",
        "wins",
        "win"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'will win'. Noun clauses can also be subjects of verbs. In this sentence, 'who will win the game' functions as the subject of 'wonder'.",
      "correctAnswer": "will win"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "They believe that ____ the truth.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "it is",
        "it"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'it is'. Noun clauses can be used as the subject of a sentence. Here, 'that it is the truth' is the subject of 'believe'.",
      "correctAnswer": "it is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "We don't know if ____.",
      "options": [
        "is raining",
        "it is raining",
        "rains"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'it is raining'. Noun clauses can act as objects of verbs. In this sentence, 'if it is raining' is the object of 'know'.",
      "correctAnswer": "it is raining"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Tell me what ____.",
      "options": [
        "you want",
        "do you want",
        "want you"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'you want'. Noun clauses can function as objects of verbs. In this sentence, 'what you want' is the object of 'tell'.",
      "correctAnswer": "you want"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The question is whether ____.",
      "options": [
        "to study",
        "study",
        "studying"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'to study'. Noun clauses can act as subjects of verbs. Here, 'whether to study' functions as the subject of the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "to study"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "Please let me know which ____.",
      "options": [
        "train is arriving",
        "arriving train",
        "train arriving"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'train is arriving'. Noun clauses can be objects of verbs. In this sentence, 'which train is arriving' is the object of 'know'.",
      "correctAnswer": "train is arriving"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I'm not sure why ____.",
      "options": [
        "she left",
        "left she",
        "she leaving"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'she left'. Noun clauses can act as objects of verbs. In this sentence, 'why she left' is the object of 'sure'.",
      "correctAnswer": "she left"
    },
    {
      "category": "Noun Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "His goal is to find out what ____.",
      "options": [
        "is happening",
        "happening",
        "does happen"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is happening'. Noun clauses can be objects of verbs. Here, 'what is happening' is the object of 'find out'.",
      "correctAnswer": "is happening"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The book ____ is on the shelf is mine.",
      "options": [
        "that",
        "who",
        "which"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that is on the shelf' is an adjective clause that describes 'book'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She lives in the house ____ has a red door.",
      "options": [
        "who",
        "which",
        "where"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'which'. In this sentence, 'which has a red door' is an adjective clause that describes 'house'.",
      "correctAnswer": "which"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The person ____ I met yesterday is my cousin.",
      "options": [
        "whom",
        "whose",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'whom'. In this sentence, 'whom I met yesterday' is an adjective clause that describes 'person'.",
      "correctAnswer": "whom"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "This is the movie ____ I was talking about.",
      "options": [
        "which",
        "that",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that I was talking about' is an adjective clause that describes 'movie'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The car ____ is parked outside is mine.",
      "options": [
        "whose",
        "when",
        "where"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'which'. In this sentence, 'which is parked outside' is an adjective clause that describes 'car'.",
      "correctAnswer": "which"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The teacher ____ taught us math is very knowledgeable.",
      "options": [
        "who",
        "when",
        "whom"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'who'. In this sentence, 'who taught us math' is an adjective clause that describes 'teacher'.",
      "correctAnswer": "who"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I visited the museum ____ has the ancient artifacts.",
      "options": [
        "where",
        "which",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'which'. In this sentence, 'which has the ancient artifacts' is an adjective clause that describes 'museum'.",
      "correctAnswer": "which"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The girl ____ bag was stolen is upset.",
      "options": [
        "whose",
        "when",
        "who"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'whose'. In this sentence, 'whose bag was stolen' is an adjective clause that describes 'girl'.",
      "correctAnswer": "whose"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I found the key ____ you were looking for.",
      "options": [
        "who",
        "which",
        "what"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that you were looking for' is an adjective clause that describes 'key'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The beach ____ we visited last summer was beautiful.",
      "options": [
        "that",
        "where",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that we visited last summer' is an adjective clause that describes 'beach'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The musician ____ performed last night was amazing.",
      "options": [
        "whom",
        "who",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'who'. In this sentence, 'who performed last night' is an adjective clause that describes 'musician'.",
      "correctAnswer": "who"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She found the cat ____ was lost.",
      "options": [
        "who",
        "which",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that was lost' is an adjective clause that describes 'cat'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The movie ____ we watched was really entertaining.",
      "options": [
        "that",
        "who",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'that'. In this sentence, 'that we watched' is an adjective clause that describes 'movie'.",
      "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "The house ____ they live in is old.",
      "options": [
        "where",
        "which",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'where'. In this sentence, 'where they live in' is an adjective clause that describes 'house'.",
      "correctAnswer": "where"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adjective Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I met a woman ____ dog was very friendly.",
      "options": [
        "which",
        "whose",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'whose'. In this sentence, 'whose dog was very friendly' is an adjective clause that describes 'woman'.",
      "correctAnswer": "whose"
    },
  
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She sings well ____ she practices daily.",
      "options": [
        "because",
        "when",
        "although"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'when'. In this sentence, 'when she practices daily' is an adverb clause that indicates the time of the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "when"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He ran fast ____ he wanted to catch the train.",
      "options": [
        "so",
        "because",
        "since"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because he wanted to catch the train' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She studies diligently ____ she wants to succeed.",
      "options": [
        "when",
        "although",
        "because"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because she wants to succeed' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "I will call you ____ I reach home.",
      "options": [
        "since",
        "when",
        "so"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'when'. In this sentence, 'when I reach home' is an adverb clause that indicates the time of the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "when"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ it rains, we won't go to the park.",
      "options": [
        "Although",
        "Because",
        "Since"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Although'. In this sentence, 'Although it rains' is an adverb clause that indicates a contrast to the main clause.",
      "correctAnswer": "Although"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He couldn't attend the meeting ____ he was sick.",
      "options": [
        "because",
        "although",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because he was sick' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She works hard ____ she wants to excel in her studies.",
      "options": [
        "when",
        "since",
        "because"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because she wants to excel in her studies' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ she arrived, the party had already started.",
      "options": [
        "When",
        "Because",
        "Since"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'When'. In this sentence, 'When she arrived' is an adverb clause that indicates the time of the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "When"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He can't swim ____ he is afraid of water.",
      "options": [
        "although",
        "when",
        "since"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because he is afraid of water' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ you finish your work, you can go home.",
      "options": [
        "Once",
        "So",
        "Although"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Once'. In this sentence, 'Once you finish your work' is an adverb clause that indicates a condition.",
      "correctAnswer": "Once"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He studied hard ____ he could pass the exam.",
      "options": [
        "although",
        "because",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'so'. In this sentence, 'so he could pass the exam' is an adverb clause that indicates the purpose of the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "____ she didn't have much experience, she managed the project well.",
      "options": [
        "Although",
        "When",
        "So"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Although'. In this sentence, 'Although she didn't have much experience' is an adverb clause that indicates a contrast to the main clause.",
      "correctAnswer": "Although"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "She sang beautifully ____ she was nervous.",
      "options": [
        "so",
        "when",
        "although"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'although'. In this sentence, 'although she was nervous' is an adverb clause that indicates a contrast to the main clause.",
      "correctAnswer": "although"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "We'll have a picnic ____ the weather is nice.",
      "options": [
        "when",
        "because",
        "so"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'if'. In this sentence, 'if the weather is nice' is an adverb clause that indicates a condition.",
      "correctAnswer": "if"
    },
    {
      "category": "Adverb Clause လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း",
      "questionText": "He didn't go to the party ____ he wasn't feeling well.",
      "options": [
        "because",
        "since",
        "when"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'because'. In this sentence, 'because he wasn't feeling well' is an adverb clause that indicates the reason for the action.",
      "correctAnswer": "because"
    },

    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The car parked outside ____ a classic Mustang.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The car parked outside' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to complete the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The painting displayed on the wall ____ a work of modern art.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The painting displayed on the wall' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to indicate its nature.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The book left on the table ____ a mystery novel.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The book left on the table' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its genre.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The tickets sold out quickly ____ for the concert.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were'. In this sentence, 'The tickets sold out quickly' is the subject, and 'were' is the correct verb to show the action of selling.",
      "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The children gathered around the campfire ____ marshmallows.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'were'. In this sentence, 'The children gathered around the campfire' is the subject, and 'were' is the correct verb to describe their activity.",
      "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The letter delivered this morning ____ an invitation.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The letter delivered this morning' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to indicate its content.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The building located downtown ____ the city's oldest library.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The building located downtown' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to provide information about the building.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The cake baked by the chef ____ a delicious dessert.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The cake baked by the chef' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its nature.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The event organized last week ____ a huge success.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'was'. In this sentence, 'The event organized last week' is the subject, and 'was' is the correct verb to indicate its outcome.",
      "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ed Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The movie released yesterday ____ an action-packed thriller.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was",
        "were"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The movie released yesterday' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its genre.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },

    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The cat sitting on the windowsill ____ a beautiful Siamese.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The cat sitting on the windowsill' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to complete the sentence.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The children playing in the park ____ having a great time.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "are"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are'. In this sentence, 'The children playing in the park' is the subject, and 'are' is the correct verb to indicate their action.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The book lying on the table ____ a thrilling mystery novel.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The book lying on the table' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its genre.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The sun shining brightly ____ a warm day.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The sun shining brightly' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe the current state.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The students working on their projects ____ focused and determined.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "are"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'are'. In this sentence, 'The students working on their projects' is the subject, and 'are' is the correct verb to describe their action.",
      "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The flowers blooming in the garden ____ a lovely fragrance.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'The flowers blooming in the garden' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct verb to indicate their possession of a fragrance.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The car racing down the highway ____ at high speed.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The car racing down the highway' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its current action.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The movie playing in the theater ____ a new release.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The movie playing in the theater' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its current status.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The rain falling outside ____ a soothing sound.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The rain falling outside' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its current action.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
      "category": "Verb-ing Clause Quiz",
      "questionText": "The river flowing through the valley ____ a picturesque view.",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'is'. In this sentence, 'The river flowing through the valley' is the subject, and 'is' is the correct verb to describe its current action.",
      "correctAnswer": "is"
    },

    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ a new laptop.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In this sentence, 'She' is the subject, and 'has' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "We ____ two cats as pets.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'We' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "He ____ a busy schedule this week.",
      "options": [
        "has",
        "have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In this sentence, 'He' is the subject, and 'has' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ three children.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'They' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "I ____ a new phone.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'I' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She ____ a younger brother.",
      "options": [
        "has",
        "have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In this sentence, 'She' is the subject, and 'has' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "They ____ a beautiful garden in their backyard.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'They' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "My parents ____ a lovely house by the beach.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'My parents' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "He ____ a good sense of humor.",
      "options": [
        "has",
        "have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In this sentence, 'He' is the subject, and 'has' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "We ____ a picnic planned for next weekend.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In this sentence, 'We' is the subject, and 'have' is the correct form to indicate possession.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },


    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "I ____ a pet dog.",
      "options": [
        "don't have",
        "doesn't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'don't have'. In the negative form for 'I', 'have' changes to 'don't have'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ a laptop.",
      "options": [
        "doesn't have",
        "don't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'doesn't have'. In the negative form for 'she', 'has' changes to 'doesn't have'.",
      "correctAnswer": "doesn't have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "They ____ a car.",
      "options": [
        "don't have",
        "doesn't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'don't have'. In the negative form for 'they', 'have' changes to 'don't have'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Do you ____ a pen?",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'have'. In the interrogative form for 'you', 'have' remains unchanged.",
      "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ they a cat?",
      "options": [
        "Do",
        "Does"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Do'. In the interrogative form for 'they', 'Do' is used.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "She ____ a bicycle.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In the negative form for 'she', 'have' changes to 'has'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ he a computer?",
      "options": [
        "Do",
        "Does"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Does'. In the interrogative form for 'he', 'Does' is used.",
      "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "We ____ a bookshelf.",
      "options": [
        "don't have",
        "doesn't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'don't have'. In the negative form for 'we', 'have' changes to 'don't have'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "____ they a new car?",
      "options": [
        "Do",
        "Does"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'Do'. In the interrogative form for 'they', 'Do' is used.",
      "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "He ____ a sister.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In the negative form for 'he', 'have' changes to 'has'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },

    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ books do you have?",
      "options": [
        "How many",
        "How much"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How many'. 'Books' is countable, so we use 'How many' to ask about the quantity of countable objects.",
      "correctAnswer": "How many"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "She ____ a smartphone?",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In the interrogative form, we use 'has' for 'she'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ milk is in the fridge?",
      "options": [
        "How much",
        "How many"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How much'. 'Milk' is uncountable, so we use 'How much' to ask about the quantity of uncountable substances.",
      "correctAnswer": "How much"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "We ____ enough time to finish the project.",
      "options": [
        "don't have",
        "doesn't have"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'don't have'. In the negative form for 'we', 'have' changes to 'don't have'.",
      "correctAnswer": "don't have"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ cups are on the table?",
      "options": [
        "How many",
        "How much"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How many'. 'Cups' is countable, so we use 'How many' to ask about the quantity of countable objects.",
      "correctAnswer": "How many"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "She ____ a pen and a pencil.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In the negative form for 'she', 'have' changes to 'has'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ time do we have before the meeting?",
      "options": [
        "How much",
        "How many"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How much'. 'Time' is uncountable, so we use 'How much' to ask about the quantity of uncountable substances.",
      "correctAnswer": "How much"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ shoes do they own?",
      "options": [
        "How many",
        "How much"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How many'. 'Shoes' is countable, so we use 'How many' to ask about the quantity of countable objects.",
      "correctAnswer": "How many"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "He ____ a lot of work to do.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'has'. In the negative form for 'he', 'have' changes to 'has'.",
      "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
      "category": "Have/has လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "____ water is in the jug?",
      "options": [
        "How much",
        "How many"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'How much'. 'Water' is uncountable, so we use 'How much' to ask about the quantity of uncountable substances.",
      "correctAnswer": "How much"
    },

    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "The _____ mountain in the range is Mount Everest.",
      "options": [
        "high",
        "higher",
        "highest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'highest'. When forming the superlative of 'high', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "highest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This book is _____ than the one I read last week.",
      "options": [
        "interesting",
        "interestinger",
        "more interesting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more interesting'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'more' + adjective to form the comparative.",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "The _____ building on the street is the new library.",
      "options": [
        "tall",
        "taller",
        "tallest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'tallest'. When forming the superlative of 'tall', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "tallest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She is a _____ singer than her sister.",
      "options": [
        "good",
        "better",
        "best"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'better'. When forming the comparative of 'good', we change the adjective to 'better'.",
      "correctAnswer": "better"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This is the _____ cake I've ever tasted.",
      "options": [
        "delicious",
        "more delicious",
        "most delicious"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most delicious'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most delicious"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Your room is _____ than mine.",
      "options": [
        "messy",
        "messier",
        "messiest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'messier'. When forming the comparative of 'messy', we add '-ier' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "messier"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This is _____ jacket I could find.",
      "options": [
        "expensive",
        "more expensive",
        "most expensive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'the most expensive'. When forming the superlative of 'expensive', we add 'the most' before the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "most expensive"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "Her performance was _____ than I expected.",
      "options": [
        "good",
        "better",
        "best"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'better'. When forming the comparative of 'good', we change the adjective to 'better'.",
      "correctAnswer": "better"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This is the _____ movie I've seen all year.",
      "options": [
        "entertaining",
        "more entertaining",
        "most entertaining"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most entertaining'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most entertaining"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "She is a _____ student than her brother.",
      "options": [
        "hard-working",
        "harder-working",
        "hardest-working"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'harder-working'. When forming the comparative of 'hard-working', we add '-er' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "harder-working"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This restaurant serves the _____ pizza in town.",
      "options": [
        "tasty",
        "more tasty",
        "most tasty"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most tasty'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most tasty"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "His handwriting is _____ than mine.",
      "options": [
        "neat",
        "neater",
        "neatest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'neater'. When forming the comparative of 'neat', we add '-er' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "neater"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This is _____ day of my life.",
      "options": [
        "happy",
        "happier",
        "happiest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'happiest'. When forming the superlative of 'happy', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "happiest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "My dog is _____ than your dog.",
      "options": [
        "big",
        "bigger",
        "biggest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'bigger'. When forming the comparative of 'big', we add '-ger' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "bigger"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၁",
      "questionText": "This is the _____ restaurant in the city.",
      "options": [
        "popular",
        "more popular",
        "most popular"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most popular'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most popular"
    },


    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: pretty",
      "options": [
        "prettier",
        "pretty",
        "prettiest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'prettier'. When forming the comparative of 'pretty', we add '-ier' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "prettier"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: tall",
      "options": [
        "tallest",
        "tall",
        "taller"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'tallest'. When forming the superlative of 'tall', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "tallest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: busy",
      "options": [
        "busiest",
        "busy",
        "busier"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'busier'. When forming the comparative of 'busy', we add '-ier' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "busier"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: expensive",
      "options": [
        "expensiver",
        "expensive",
        "most expensive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most expensive'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most expensive"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: beautiful",
      "options": [
        "beautifuler",
        "beautiful",
        "more beautiful"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more beautiful'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'more' + adjective to form the comparative.",
      "correctAnswer": "more beautiful"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: delicious",
      "options": [
        "deliciouser",
        "delicious",
        "most delicious"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most delicious'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most delicious"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: strong",
      "options": [
        "stronger",
        "strong",
        "strongest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'stronger'. When forming the comparative of 'strong', we add '-er' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "stronger"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: famous",
      "options": [
        "famouser",
        "famous",
        "most famous"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most famous'. For adjectives with two syllables ending in '-y', we change '-y' to '-iest' to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most famous"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: hot",
      "options": [
        "hotter",
        "hot",
        "hottest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'hotter'. When forming the comparative of 'hot', we add '-er' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "hotter"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: clever",
      "options": [
        "cleverer",
        "clever",
        "cleverest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'cleverest'. When forming the superlative of 'clever', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "cleverest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: happy",
      "options": [
        "happyer",
        "happier",
        "happiest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'happier'. When forming the comparative of 'happy', we add '-ier' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "happier"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: quiet",
      "options": [
        "quietest",
        "quiet",
        "quietier"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'quietest'. When forming the superlative of 'quiet', we add '-est' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "quietest"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: large",
      "options": [
        "larger",
        "large",
        "largest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'larger'. When forming the comparative of 'large', we add '-er' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "larger"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: interesting",
      "options": [
        "interesting",
        "interestinger",
        "most interesting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most interesting'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most interesting"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct comparative form of the adjective: funny",
      "options": [
        "funnier",
        "funny",
        "funniest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'funnier'. When forming the comparative of 'funny', we add '-ier' to the adjective.",
      "correctAnswer": "funnier"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၂",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct superlative form of the adjective: comfortable",
      "options": [
        "comfortabler",
        "comfortable",
        "most comfortable"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'most comfortable'. For adjectives with three or more syllables, we use 'most' + adjective to form the superlative.",
      "correctAnswer": "most comfortable"
    },
  
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Choose the correct form: This car is ___________ the one we saw yesterday.",
      "options": [
        "as nice",
        "nicer than",
        "nicest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'nicer than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "nicer than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Select the appropriate option: Her performance is __________ mine.",
      "options": [
        "as good as",
        "better than",
        "best"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'as good as'. When comparing things as equal, we use 'as + adjective + as' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "as good as"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Choose the right form: The weather is ___________ it was last week.",
      "options": [
        "as warm as",
        "warmer than",
        "warmest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'warmer than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "warmer than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Pick the correct option: This restaurant is ___________ the one we visited last time.",
      "options": [
        "as expensive as",
        "more expensive than",
        "most expensive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more expensive than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "more expensive than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Choose the suitable option: The movie was __________ I expected.",
      "options": [
        "not as interesting as",
        "interesting as",
        "most interesting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'not as interesting as'. When comparing things as unequal, we use 'not as + adjective + as' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "not as interesting as"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Select the correct form: The red dress is ___________ the blue one.",
      "options": [
        "as bright as",
        "brighter than",
        "brightest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'brighter than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "brighter than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Pick the right option: This book is ___________ the one I read last month.",
      "options": [
        "as interesting as",
        "more interesting than",
        "most interesting"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more interesting than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Choose the appropriate form: The new phone is ___________ the old one.",
      "options": [
        "as expensive as",
        "more expensive than",
        "most expensive"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more expensive than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "more expensive than"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Select the suitable option: This city is ___________ I imagined.",
      "options": [
        "not as big as",
        "big as",
        "biggest"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'not as big as'. When comparing things as unequal, we use 'not as + adjective + as' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "not as big as"
    },
    {
      "category": "Comparison လေ့ကျင့်ခန်း ၃",
      "questionText": "Pick the correct form: The chocolate cake is ___________ the vanilla one.",
      "options": [
        "as delicious as",
        "more delicious than",
        "most delicious"
      ],
      "explanation": "The correct answer is 'more delicious than'. When comparing two things, we use 'comparative + than' structure.",
      "correctAnswer": "more delicious than"
    }
  
]

